{"quiz":{"for-kids":{"complete":true,"questions":[{"answers":["sloshy","Peter Frampton","Limozeen","Taranchula"],"question":"What is NOT one of Strong Bads favorite bands in the Internet cartoon Homestar Runner?","type":"choice","answer":"sloshy"},{"answers":["Rampion","Turnip","Lettuce","Safflower"],"question":"Speaking of the famous fairy tale, that girl with the long hair was named which of these plants?","type":"choice","answer":"Rampion"},{"answers":["Collects the finished thread","Powers the wheel","Twists the fibres into a thread","Sorts the finished threads"],"question":"Sleeping Beauty pricked her finger on the part of a spinning wheel that does this.","type":"choice","answer":"Twists the fibres into a thread"},{"answers":["Glass shoes sound like something a princess would wear.","Vair (fur), was mistaken for verre (glass).","They were a symbol of her purity.","Glass shoes were worn by royalty."],"question":"Why does Cinderella wear a glass slipper?","type":"choice","answer":"Glass shoes sound like something a princess would wear."},{"answers":["","Foam on the waves.","",""],"question":"The Little Mermaid refused to kill the prince, so she eventually ends up as this.","type":"choice","answer":"A daughter of the air."},{"answers":["Hemophiliac lips.","Rosaceae cheeks.","Ice crystal eyes.","Wooden hair."],"question":"Only one of the following descriptions of the features of Snow White is true.  Can you spot it?","type":"choice","answer":"Wooden hair."},{"answers":["Dried stalks of marsh plant.","Dry stalks of grass.","Dry stalks of corn.","Dry stalks of wheat."],"question":"Referring to a well-known fairy tale, the millers daughter had to spin what?","type":"choice","answer":"Dry stalks of wheat."},{"answers":["England","Italy","Eastern Europe","The Middle East"],"question":"The witch in Hansel and Gretel was probably raised in this part of the world.","type":"choice","answer":"Eastern Europe"},{"answers":["Saladin - righteousness","Fallow - pale in colour","Falada - to speak","Salada - white as salt"],"question":"Referring to the popular fairy tale, what is the name of the goose girls enchanted horse?","type":"choice","answer":"Falada - to speak"},{"answers":["Belladonna","Urticaria","Belonidae","Urticaceae"],"question":"Poor Eliza of the famous fairy tale, had to make eleven shirts of what plant?","type":"choice","answer":"Urticaceae"},{"answers":["6","8","3","none"],"question":"How many siblings does Ron have?","type":"choice","answer":"6"},{"answers":["Being poor","Being the youngest boy in his family","Being unpopular","Not being in Slytherin"],"question":"What does Ron hate the most about himself?","type":"choice","answer":"Being poor"},{"answers":["Parvati Patil","Padma Patil","Hermione Granger","Ginny Weasley"],"question":"Who does Ron take to the Yule ball?","type":"choice","answer":"Padma Patil"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Rons mom is part of the order of the phoenix.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Ronald Perkins Weasley","Ronald Arthur Weasley","Ronald J. Weasley","Ronald Bilius Weasley"],"question":"What is Rons full name?","type":"choice","answer":"Ronald Bilius Weasley"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Has Ron ever been dead?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Oliver Wood","Cedric Diggory","Viktor Krum","Harry Potter"],"question":"Who is Rons idol?","type":"choice","answer":"Viktor Krum"},{"answers":["Goblet of Fire","Never","Half-Blood Prince","Sorcerers Stone"],"question":"In which of the first six books does Ron face Voldemort?","type":"choice","answer":"Never"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"Which charm did Doby the House Elf use to get Harry Potter in huge trouble with his Uncle?","type":"choice","answer":"A hover charm"},{"answers":["Albus Abelforth Wulfric Brian Dumbledore","Albus Nicholas Abelforth Dumbledore","Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore","Albus Wulfric Nicholas Dumbledore"],"question":"What is the full name of Harry Potters Headmaster, as revealed in the 5th book?","type":"choice","answer":"Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"},{"answers":["Lacewing flies, leeches, powdered bicorn horn, knotgrass, fluxweed, and boomslang skin","Porcupine quills, leeches, lacewing flies, valerian roots, and boomslang skin","Powdered dragon horn, moonstone, lacewing flies, boomslang skin, dried nettles, and valerian roots","Moonstone, lacewing flies, boomslang skin, dried nettles, knotgrass, and bubotuber pus"],"question":"Aside from a bit of the person you wish to become, what are the other ingredients used to make Polyjuice Potion, as seen in the 2nd book of Harry Potter?","type":"choice","answer":"Lacewing flies, leeches, powdered bicorn horn, knotgrass, fluxweed, and boomslang skin"},{"answers":["Swedish Short-Snout","Welsh Green","Hungarian Horntail","Chinese Fireball"],"question":"In the first task of the Triwizard Tournament (Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire ), each champion has to fight a different breed of dragon.  Which dragon does Fleur Delacour face?","type":"choice","answer":"Welsh Green"},{"answers":["His patronus is strong enough to complete its intended task","His patronus is consistent enough to always have a defined shape to it","His patronus is so dependable that it becomes the same animal everytime","His patronus is so well developed it has a commanding presence whenever it is conjured"],"question":"At Harry Potters trial during the 5th book, Madam Bones refers to Harrys patronus a corporal patronus.  What makes Harrys patronus corporal?","type":"choice","answer":"His patronus is consistent enough to always have a defined shape to it"},{"answers":["He gets a pigs tail","He breaks out in horrible zits","His tongue is enlarged to almost 4 feet","He gets attacted by dementors"],"question":"Harry Potters Dudley Dursley has had many traumatic encounters with wizards.  Which of the following has not happened to him?","type":"choice","answer":"He breaks out in horrible zits"},{"answers":["Self-Inking Quills","Fever Fudge","Coughing Cakes","Pygmy Puff"],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, Fred and George invented a lot of products for their store, Weasleys Wizard Wheezes.  Which of the following products was not one invited by Fred and George?","type":"choice","answer":"Coughing Cakes"},{"answers":["Arithmancy","Astronomy","Ancient Runes","Alchemy"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, Hermione is given a time turner so she is able to make it to all of her extra classes.  Which of the following classes does she not take?","type":"choice","answer":"Alchemy"},{"answers":["Hermoine","Ron","Dumbledore","Hagrid"],"question":"Who was the last person Harry talked to in the book?","type":"choice","answer":"Hermoine"},{"answers":["Nothing","An owl","",""],"question":"What did the Dursleys send Harry for Christmas?","type":"choice","answer":"A fifty pence piece"},{"answers":["Ginny","George","Ginger","Grace"],"question":"Rons sisters name is?","type":"choice","answer":"Ginny"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Hermoine broke her wrist when she fell off a broom.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Pee-wee","Peeves","Pippy","Petry"],"question":"Who is the poltergeist that lives at Hogwarts?","type":"choice","answer":"Peeves"},{"answers":["Every Flavor Jellybeans","Lemon Drop","Cockroach Cluster","Mr. Goodbar"],"question":"What type of candy did Dumbledore offer McGonagell?","type":"choice","answer":"Lemon Drop"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Dudleys gang consisted of Piers, dennis, Malcolm and Gordon.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Stonewall High","Yale","Stonebridge High","St. Brutus"],"question":"What was the name of the Muggle school Harry was to attend?","type":"choice","answer":"Stonewall High"},{"answers":["Flourish  Blotts","Ollivanders","J.C. Penneys","Madame Malkins"],"question":"Where did Harry buy his wand?","type":"choice","answer":"Ollivanders"},{"answers":["Proffesor Snape","Lucious Malfoy","Draco Malfoy","Lord Voldemort"],"question":"Who breaks Harry Potters nose in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, the sixth novel in the series?","type":"choice","answer":"Draco Malfoy"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Does Draco Malfoy attempt to kill Dumbledore in the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Initially Harry Potter and Ron did not like Hermione and considered her annoying, interfering and snobby.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Nobody","Ginny Weasley","Cho Chang","Hermione Granger"],"question":"Who does Harry Potter kiss in the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, after Gryffindor wins the Quidditch Cup?","type":"choice","answer":"Ginny Weasley"},{"answers":["Luna Lovegood","Marietta Edgecombe","Cho Chang","Ginny Weasly"],"question":"This fictional character suggests the name Dumbledores Army for the organization started by Harry, Hermione, and Ron in the book Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.","type":"choice","answer":"Ginny Weasly"},{"answers":["Harry potter and the Order of the Phoniex","Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince","Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets","Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"],"question":"In which book of the Harry Potter series, Harry, Ron and Hermione start attending the Divination class, taught by Professor Trelawney?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"},{"answers":["1999","None of these","2000","2001"],"question":"In what year did J.K. Rowling receive an OBE (Order of the British Empire) from the Queen of England?","type":"choice","answer":"2000"},{"answers":["Quill pen","Fireplace","Crayon","Horn book"],"question":"Which of the following items cannot be found in a colonial classroom?","type":"choice","answer":"Crayon"},{"answers":["Skateboarding","Using a dishwasher","Reading McGuffey","Ordering pizza"],"question":"Colonial people spend some of their free time doing which of these?","type":"choice","answer":"Reading McGuffey"},{"answers":["Went to school","Worked on his autobiography","Worked on many inventions, including electricity","Worked as an apprentice"],"question":"From age 12 to 21, American activist and politician Benjamin Franklin did what?","type":"choice","answer":"Worked as an apprentice"},{"answers":["Jane Addams","Harriet Tubman","Betty Ross","Florence Nightingale"],"question":"In 1889, this person founded the Hull House, one of the first settlement houses in the U.S.","type":"choice","answer":"Jane Addams"},{"answers":["I have a dream.","Give me liberty or give me death.","I have not yet begun to fight.","I shall return."],"question":"Which of the following is a famous quote by John Paul Jones, the well-known American naval hero from the American Revolutionary War?","type":"choice","answer":"I have not yet begun to fight."},{"answers":["Emancipation Proclamation","Louisiana Purchase","Declaration of Independence","Boston Tea Party"],"question":"Which of the following events is associated with Independence Day?","type":"choice","answer":"Declaration of Independence"},{"answers":["1588","1498","1600","1763"],"question":"What year did Columbus first arrive on American land?","type":"choice","answer":"1498"},{"answers":["Dolphin","Seal","Anteater","Kangaroo"],"question":"You can see this animal around ant-hill. It is almost 6 feet long and it likes to eat ants.","type":"choice","answer":"Anteater"},{"answers":["Fox","Bear","Cheetah","Horse"],"question":"It is a big animal with brown fur and it likes eating fish and honey. It has 42 teeth.","type":"choice","answer":"Bear"},{"answers":["Ant","Fly","Cockroach","Grasshopper"],"question":"This is a repulsive insect either black or brown. It can live a couple of weeks with its head cut off.","type":"choice","answer":"Cockroach"},{"answers":["Elephant","Rabbit","Bear","Horse"],"question":"This is a big and grey animal with wide ears and a trunk. It cannot hop.","type":"choice","answer":"Elephant"},{"answers":["Chow Chow","Pitbull","Hound","Setter"],"question":"This is a fluffy dog. It has a black-black or purple tongue.","type":"choice","answer":"Chow Chow"},{"answers":["Giraffe","Elephant","Zebra","Camel"],"question":"This animal lives in Africa. It has a really long neck and eats leaves. It produces almost no sounds.","type":"choice","answer":"Giraffe"},{"answers":["Cat","Anteater","Rat","Weasel"],"question":"This animal is similar to a mouse but it is bigger. It can give birth to more than 160 babies in a year.","type":"choice","answer":"Rat"},{"answers":["Snakes","Frogs","Fish","Eel"],"question":"These animals are long and slim. They creep. Most of them can go an entire year without eating at all!","type":"choice","answer":"Snakes"},{"answers":["Mackerel","Dolphins","Salmon","Tuna fish"],"question":"These animals live in the sea. They are very friendly to humans. Although they resemble fish, they will drown if kept underwater for too long.","type":"choice","answer":"Dolphins"},{"answers":["Skunk","Turbot","Horse","Deer"],"question":"When this animal wants to defend itself, it throws a nasty smell toward its aggressor. This smell can be detected by a human a mile away.","type":"choice","answer":"Skunk"},{"answers":["Divination","Arithmancy","Muggle Studies","Potions"],"question":"Which subject was Hermione not taking at 9am?","type":"choice","answer":"Potions"},{"answers":["None of these is correct","9","13","12"],"question":"How many people where at the dinner table before Professor Trelawney joined them?","type":"choice","answer":"12"},{"answers":["Batgut Buckshot","Bathilda Baghide","Hilda Bagshot","Bathilda Bagshot"],"question":"Who wrote A History of Magic?","type":"choice","answer":"Bathilda Bagshot"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Peter Pettigrew has his nose put in a box.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Professor Lupin","The Bloody Baron","Harry","Professor Lockhart"],"question":"Who shot gum up Peeves left nostril?","type":"choice","answer":"Professor Lupin"},{"answers":["James - Antlers","Pettigrew - Wormtail","Lupin - Moony","Sirius - Padfoot"],"question":"Which pairing is not correct?","type":"choice","answer":"James - Antlers"},{"answers":["Scrimgeour","Weasly","Umbridge","Fudge"],"question":"What is the Minister of Magics name in book six?","type":"choice","answer":"Scrimgeour"},{"answers":["no one","Bill","Lupin","Ron"],"question":"Who is Tonks in love with?","type":"choice","answer":"Lupin"},{"answers":["Ginny","Luna","Romilda","Cho"],"question":"Who has the hots for Harry in the first half of the book?","type":"choice","answer":"Romilda"},{"answers":["Veritaserum","Draught of Living Death","Draught of Death","Felix Felicis"],"question":"Which potion did Harry make to win a bottle of Liquid Luckin Chapter 9?","type":"choice","answer":"Draught of Living Death"},{"answers":["Lily","Mekare","Jane","Merope"],"question":"She is Tom Riddles mother.","type":"choice","answer":"Merope"},{"answers":["abysmal","caput draconis","abstinence","abstraction"],"question":"This was the password to the Griffindore Tower after Christmas break.","type":"choice","answer":"abstinence"},{"answers":["Neville","Ron","They all were","Harry"],"question":"Who was not at Hermiones table in Herbology?","type":"choice","answer":"Neville"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Tom Riddle worked for Florrish and Blott after he left Hogwarts.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["J.R. Rolling","J.R. Tolkien","J.K. Rowling","Gilderoy Lockhart"],"question":"Who is the author of the Harry Potter series of books?","type":"choice","answer":"J.K. Rowling"},{"answers":["2000","1989","2001","1998"],"question":"Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, the second book in the Harry Potter series, was published in what year?","type":"choice","answer":"1998"},{"answers":["a house dwarf","a house Imp","a house nymph","a house elf"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, during the summer break Harry gets a visit from a character named Dobby. What kind of creature is Dobby?","type":"choice","answer":"a house elf"},{"answers":["Lupin","Stan Shunpike","Gilderoy Lockhart","Rowling"],"question":"This fictional character, introduced in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, was teacher of the class called Defense Against the Dark Artsand five-time winner of Witch Weeklys Most Charming Smile Award.","type":"choice","answer":"Gilderoy Lockhart"},{"answers":["a black willow tree","a whomping willow tree","a deadwood Tree","a weeping willow tree"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry and Ron take a ride with the flying Ford Anglia and crash into what kind of tree?","type":"choice","answer":"a whomping willow tree"},{"answers":["Moaning Molly","Moaning Martha","Moaning Myrtle","Moaning Mary"],"question":"This fictional character from the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets is a ghost ,who haunts the second floor girls lavatory at Hogwarts School for Witchcraft and Wizardry.","type":"choice","answer":"Moaning Myrtle"},{"answers":["Cho Chang","None of these","Draco Malfoy","Ginny Weasley"],"question":"Which character of the Harry Potter series of books opens the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Ginny Weasley"},{"answers":["parseltongue","none of these","parsellanguage","parselspeak"],"question":"What is the language of snakes, spoken by some of the characters in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"parseltongue"},{"answers":["Wales","Scotland","England","Northern Ireland"],"question":"The fictional Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry is geographically located in which part of the United Kingdom?","type":"choice","answer":"Scotland"},{"answers":["Workers of the Postal Union 151","Owl post","United Parcel Service","Postal carriage"],"question":"How is the wizarding worlds newspaper, The Daily Prophet, delivered each morning in the Harry Potter novels?","type":"choice","answer":"Owl post"},{"answers":["Internet","Fireplaces","Toilets","Fedex"],"question":"According to the Harry Potter books, the Floo Network, or traveling using floo powder, means using what method of transportation?","type":"choice","answer":"Fireplaces"},{"answers":["Eagle","Panda","Serpent","Lion"],"question":"Which of the following animals does NOT symbolize one of the four Hogwarts Houses, described in the Harry Potter series of books?","type":"choice","answer":"Panda"},{"answers":["750 meter highrise, which is the tallest building in the wizarding world.","Wigwam","Wooden cabin",""],"question":"Hagrid, the keeper of the keys at Hogwarts in the Harry Potter books, lives in this building on the edge of the Forbidden Forest.","type":"choice","answer":"Wooden cabin"},{"answers":["Ford Anglia","Apache helicopter","Boeing 767","Flying carpet"],"question":"In what type of vehicle did Ron and Harry Potter fly to Hogwarts from London?","type":"choice","answer":"Ford Anglia"},{"answers":["Monopoly","Checkers","Chess","Scrabble"],"question":"While looking for the Sorcerers Stone, Ron and Harry Potter must play a life-size version of this game.","type":"choice","answer":"Chess"},{"answers":["Hydroplane","Motorcycle","Lamborghini","Hot air balloon"],"question":"This flying machine was owned by Sirius Black and used by Hagrid in his first appearance on Privet Drive.","type":"choice","answer":"Motorcycle"},{"answers":["","An eagle and a lion","","An eagle and a horse"],"question":"In the Harry Potter universe, a hippogriff is a hybrid of what two animals?","type":"choice","answer":"An eagle and a horse"},{"answers":["Women","Snakes","Centaurs","Elfs"],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, if a person is a parselmouth, then he or she is able to understand what?","type":"choice","answer":"Snakes"},{"answers":["how tall the tree is","how old the tree is","whether or not it is a fruit bearing tree","what type of tree it is"],"question":"What do the rings on a tree tell us?","type":"choice","answer":"how old the tree is"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The path in which electricity travels is called an electric circuit.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Seasons change because the Earth is getting closer and further from the sun.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Stars vanish during the day.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"There are 4 basic conditions needed to produce an echo.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Peter, Annie, Alan, Lucy","Peter, Susan, Edmund, Sydney","Peter, Susan, Edmund, Lucy","Peter, Sally, Edward, Lucinda"],"question":"What are the names of the four children in the story The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?","type":"choice","answer":"Peter, Susan, Edmund, Lucy"},{"answers":["The Red Witch","The Evil Witch","The Terrible Witch of the West","The White Witch"],"question":"Which character is the enemy of the four children in the movie The Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?","type":"choice","answer":"The White Witch"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, Susan is the oldest of the four children.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Turkish Delight","Laffy Taffy","Jolly Rancher","Turkish Joy"],"question":"In the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe Edmund asked if the White Witch had what candy?","type":"choice","answer":"Turkish Delight"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Is it true that in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, Lucy discovered the wardrobe, while the children were playing hide and seek?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["green","brown","hazel","blue"],"question":"What was the colour of Susans eyes in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?","type":"choice","answer":"blue"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Is Peter the second of the Pevensie children to enter Narnia in the film The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The action in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe begins in 1940 during a German bombing raid of London.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Taurus","Tamus","Tumnus","Timus"],"question":"What is the name of the faun that Lucy meets in The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?","type":"choice","answer":"Tumnus"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The lion that the children meet in the end of the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobeis called Aslan.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Moaning Myrthle","Peeves","Nearly-headless Nick","The Bloody Baron"],"question":"Which of the following characters in the Harry Potter books is a poltergeist?","type":"choice","answer":"Peeves"},{"answers":["Felix Felicis","Polyjuice Potion","none of these","Avada Kedava"],"question":"What is the name of the potion that grants good luck, mentioned in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Felix Felicis"},{"answers":["Hermione","Cho","Ginny","Blaise"],"question":"Which of these characters kissed Harry after a lesson of DA in Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?","type":"choice","answer":"Cho"},{"answers":["The Order of the Phoenix","The Headless Hunt","The Triwizard Cup","The DA"],"question":"What group did Nearly-headless Nick never become a part of in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"The Headless Hunt"},{"answers":["James Potter, Remus Lupin, Sirius Black","James Potter, Remus Lupin","James Potter, Sirius Black, Peter Pettigrew","James Potter only"],"question":"Which of the following characters are described as trustworthy in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"James Potter, Remus Lupin, Sirius Black"},{"answers":["Albus Percival Dumbledore","Albus Wulfric Dumbledore","Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore","He never revealed his full name in the books"],"question":"According to the Harry Potter books, what is the full name of Dumbledore, the headmaster of Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry?","type":"choice","answer":"Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Dumbledore was in contact with Sirius Black in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Stir clockwise until the potion turns as clear as water","Add a counterclockwise stir after every seventh clockwise stir","Stir counterclockwise until the potion turns as clear as water","Add a clockwise stir after every seventh counterclockwise stir"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, the half-blood prince tells Harry to do what to his potion?","type":"choice","answer":"Add a clockwise stir after every seventh counterclockwise stir"},{"answers":["Manticore","Unicorn","Hippogriff","Bird"],"question":"What kind of creature was Buckbeak from the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"Hippogriff"},{"answers":["Dudley","Ron","Hermione","Ms. Weasley"],"question":"Who was the last person to talk to Harry at the end of Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Hermione"},{"answers":["Fluffy","Norbert","Aragog","Fang"],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, what is the name of Hagrids three-headed dog?","type":"choice","answer":"Fluffy"},{"answers":["Sirius Black","Remus Lupin","Peter Pettigrew","James Potter"],"question":"According to the Harry Potter books, who is Harrys godfather?","type":"choice","answer":"Sirius Black"},{"answers":["Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone","Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince","Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix","She doesnt get fired in the books"],"question":"In what book of the Harry Potter series does professor Trelawney get fired?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix"},{"answers":["Hermione Cassandra Granger","It was never mentioned.","Hermione James Dumbledore","Hermione Jean Granger"],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, what is Harrys classmate Hermiones full name?","type":"choice","answer":"Hermione Jean Granger"},{"answers":["Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban","Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire","Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets","Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone"],"question":"In which movie did Hermione Granger say the following:\r","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone"},{"answers":["that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Sirius Black","that it was given to Harry by Dumbledore because he felt bad after Harrys broom was demolished by the Whomping Willow","that it was amazing and wanted to be the first to ride it after Harry","that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Lucius Malfoy who was still angry about the loss of his House Elf"],"question":"What did Hermione Granger, a character from the Harry Potter series, think about the Firebolt?","type":"choice","answer":"that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Sirius Black"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"It is stated in the Harry Potter books that Hermione Grangers parents are teachers.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Was Hermione able to see the Thresals in Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the Harry Potter series, Hermiones full name is Hermione Denise Granger.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Baseball Wand","Baseball Bat","Baseball Raquet","Baseball Club"],"question":"What is the wooden stick used to hit a baseball called?","type":"choice","answer":"Baseball Bat"},{"answers":["Green","White","Black","Blue"],"question":"What color is a major league baseball?","type":"choice","answer":"White"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Should you wear a helmet while hitting a baseball?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Home Run","Stolen Base","Hat Trick","3 Pointer"],"question":"What is it called when you hit a baseball out of the park?","type":"choice","answer":"Home Run"},{"answers":["Baseball Helmet","Baseball Glove","Baseball Mittens","Baseball Shoes"],"question":"What do you wear on your hand when playing the field in baseball?","type":"choice","answer":"Baseball Glove"},{"answers":["Catcher","Short Stop","Manager","Pitcher"],"question":"In baseball, what is the name of the player who squats behind the hitter and catches the ball?","type":"choice","answer":"Catcher"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"When you run the bases in baseball you should run from 3rd base to 1st base.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Coach","Catcher","Short Stop","Pitcher"],"question":"What is the player who throws the ball to the hitter called in baseball?","type":"choice","answer":"Pitcher"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Baseball is usually played indoors.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["$44","$35","$39","$37"],"question":"Casey has 2 ten dollar bills, 3 five dollar bills, and 4 one dollar bills. How much money does Casey have altogether?","type":"choice","answer":"$39"},{"answers":["XXXXXXXX","XXXXXXX","XXXXXXXXX","XXXXXXXXXX"],"question":"What would be next in this pattern:  XX, XXXX, XXXXXX, ________?","type":"choice","answer":"XXXXXXXX"},{"answers":["Reeses Pieces, Nerds, and Gum","Pepsi and Gum","Pepsi and Nerds","Reeses Pieces and Gum"],"question":"Reeses Pieces cost $0.60. Nerds cost $0.35. Pepsi costs $0.90. Gum costs $0.45. I have $1.25, and want to spend all of my money. What should I buy?","type":"choice","answer":"Pepsi and Nerds"},{"answers":["26","35","36","82"],"question":"Chad and Jason have a collection of comic books. Chad has 23 books. Together, Chad and Jason have a total of 59 books. How many books does Jason have?","type":"choice","answer":"36"},{"answers":["30","35","45","40"],"question":"Leah is making chocolate chip cookies. She has 6 groups of 5 chocolate chips each. If she adds one more group of 5 chocolate chips, how many chocolate chips will she have?","type":"choice","answer":"35"},{"answers":["$0.60","$0.65","$0.70","$0.75"],"question":"Stephanie has $0.85. She gives a quarter to Jennifer. In return, Jennifer gives Stephanie a dime. How much money does Stephanie have now?","type":"choice","answer":"$0.70"},{"answers":["7:35 a.m.","7:45 a.m.","8:25 a.m","7:25 a.m."],"question":"Mike has to be to school at 8:00 a.m. If it takes him 25 minutes to walk to school, what time should he leave?","type":"choice","answer":"7:35 a.m."},{"answers":["Prince Caspian","The Boy and His Horse","The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe","The Voyage of the Dawn Treader"],"question":"The Chronicles of Narnia, written by C.S. Lewis, is a series of seven fantasy novels. Which of the following is not one of the books in this series?","type":"choice","answer":"The Boy and His Horse"},{"answers":["Caspian","Telmar","Eustace","Digory"],"question":"In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, published in 1952, Edmund and Lucy Pevensie return to Narnia along with their younger cousin named what?","type":"choice","answer":"Eustace"},{"answers":["The Last Battle","Prince Caspian","The Voyage of the Dawn Treader","The Silver Chair"],"question":"There comes a point when Peter, Susan, Edmund, and Lucy Pevensie are no longer allowed to visit Narnia because they are too old. So the lion calls their young cousin back to Narnia together with Jill, a fellow student of his. This happens in which book of The Chronicles of Narnia series?","type":"choice","answer":"The Silver Chair"},{"answers":["Lucy","Susan","Edmund","Peter"],"question":"Which of the Pevensie children is lured into teaming up with the White Witch in the novel The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?","type":"choice","answer":"Edmund"},{"answers":["Ape","Centaur","Unicorn","Faun"],"question":"In The Last Battle chronicles, which earned C.S. Lewis a Carnegie Medal, two children return to save Narnia from Shift who tricks the donkey Puzzle into impersonating the Great Lion. What kind of creature is Shift?","type":"choice","answer":"Ape"},{"answers":["water ski","bungy jump","walk a tightrope","snow ski"],"question":"What can Bungy the budgie do?","type":"choice","answer":"water ski"},{"answers":["Hermione","Sirius Black","Arthur Weasley","Molly Weasley"],"question":"Who sent Harry a letter in Chapter 2 telling him not to do any more magic, or to surrender his wand?","type":"choice","answer":"Arthur Weasley"},{"answers":["Sirius Black","Lucius Malfoy","Arthur Weasly","Albus Dumbledore"],"question":"Cornelius Fudge thinks that who wants to be the Minister of Magic?","type":"choice","answer":"Albus Dumbledore"},{"answers":["Regulus","Tom","Ronald","Remus"],"question":"This person is Siriuss brother.","type":"choice","answer":"Regulus"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Luna Lovegood was reading the Quippler on the Hogwarts Express.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Llewellyn","Corwin","Blaise","Diedre"],"question":"What ward was Arthur Weasly in while at St Mungos?","type":"choice","answer":"Llewellyn"},{"answers":["Jane","Marie","Barbara","Mary"],"question":"This is Professor Umbridges middle name.","type":"choice","answer":"Jane"},{"answers":["Urg","Gurg","Gurrl","Ugh"],"question":"A giant chief is called this.","type":"choice","answer":"Gurg"},{"answers":["his Grandmother","no one","his Grandfather","his parents"],"question":"Who had Neville Longbottom seen die?","type":"choice","answer":"his Grandfather"},{"answers":["Cho","Neville","Luna","Ron"],"question":"Who did not go with Harry to the Ministry of Magic to rescue Black?","type":"choice","answer":"Cho"},{"answers":["Mr. Fast Food","Mr. Meaty","Mr. Meat","Dr. Burger"],"question":"Josh and Parker star on this Nickelodeon show which takes place mostly at a fast food restaurant. What is the name of the show?","type":"choice","answer":"Mr. Meaty"},{"answers":["Jimmy Neutron","Drake and Josh","Neutron, Boy Genius","The fairly odd parents"],"question":"Which of these Nickelodeon animated shows stars a big headed kid who also has a very big brain?","type":"choice","answer":"Jimmy Neutron"},{"answers":["Water","Fire","Air","Light"],"question":"In the show Jimmy Neutron, Jimmy goes to Mars in search of a major power source and runs into some huge rock creatures living on Mars. What substance are these creatures vulnerable to?","type":"choice","answer":"Water"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Actor Drake Bell from the Nickelodeon show Drake and Josh founded a band named Drake 24/7 in real life.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Ned Bigby","Simon Nelson Cook","Nobody dares her that","Billy Loomer"],"question":"In Neds Declassified School Survival Guide, who dares Moze to wear a frilly dress with flowers for 48 hours?","type":"choice","answer":"Nobody dares her that"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Actress Miranda Cosgrove plays Megan in the hit Nickelodeon show Drake and Josh.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["","Jean-Claude Van Damme","Sam","Bam-Bam"],"question":"Complete this line from the classic childrens book Green Eggs and Ham:\r","type":"choice","answer":"Sam"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The book Green Eggs and Ham was first published in 1952.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Fourth","Second","First","Third"],"question":"Where did Green Eggs and Ham rank according to Publishers Weekly 2001 list of best selling childrens books of all-time?","type":"choice","answer":"Fourth"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Rev. Jesse Jackson once read Green Eggs and Ham aloud on the late Night show Saturday Night Live.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Dog with Chicken Pox","Bag of Rocks","Clock","Fox"],"question":"Complete this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:\r","type":"choice","answer":"Fox"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The book Green Eggs and Ham contains only 50 different words.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Line at the DMV","Jeep","Bucket of boiled beets","Car"],"question":"What word is missing in this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:\r","type":"choice","answer":"Car"},{"answers":["Hat","Helmet","Wig","Shoe"],"question":"What should you wear on your head when you play American football?","type":"choice","answer":"Helmet"},{"answers":["Quarterback","Running back","Kicker","Tight End"],"question":"In American football, the player who throws the ball to the other players on the field is called what?","type":"choice","answer":"Quarterback"},{"answers":["Helmet","Stick","Padding","Football"],"question":"Which of these items is not used in an American football game?","type":"choice","answer":"Stick"},{"answers":["Touchdown","Three Pointer","Home Run","Hat Trick"],"question":"What is the main method of scoring in American football?","type":"choice","answer":"Touchdown"},{"answers":["Patriots","Dolphins","Yankees","Jets"],"question":"What is the professional team of Miami in American football called?","type":"choice","answer":"Dolphins"},{"answers":["Court","Rink","Diamond","Field"],"question":"What do you call the grassy area on which an American football game is played?","type":"choice","answer":"Field"},{"answers":["Brown and white","Green and yellow","Pink and purple","Blue and red"],"question":"What is the color of a traditional American football?","type":"choice","answer":"Brown and white"},{"answers":["2","4","5","6"],"question":"How many points is a touchdown worth in American football?","type":"choice","answer":"6"},{"answers":["Rectangle","Square","Oval","Round"],"question":"What is the shape of a traditional American football?","type":"choice","answer":"Oval"},{"answers":["Wide Receiver","Quarterback","Tight End","Coach"],"question":"What do you call the man or woman who runs a football team and tells the players what to do?","type":"choice","answer":"Coach"},{"answers":["1889","1985","1989","1885"],"question":"In what year did Disney release the film The Little Mermaid?","type":"choice","answer":"1989"},{"answers":["Marianne","Vanessa","Janice","Carlotta"],"question":"What was the name of the housemaid that served dinner on Ariels first night in the palace in the movie The Little Mermaid?","type":"choice","answer":"Carlotta"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Ursula, one of the characters in the Disney movie The Little Mermaid, is a cecaelia sea witch.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Matilda","Vanessa","Gertrude","Louise"],"question":"What name did Ursula adopt while in disguise in the movie The Little Mermaid?","type":"choice","answer":"Vanessa"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Buddy Hackett provided the voice of Flounder in the movie The Little Mermaid.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The film The Little Mermaid grossed approximately $200,000,000.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The first line in the movie The Little Mermaid was Flounder, quit being such a guppy!.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Nov. 18 1989","Nov. 29 1990","Nov. 15 1989","Nov. 15 1990"],"question":"When was the film The Little Mermaid released in Germany?","type":"choice","answer":"Nov. 29 1990"},{"answers":["Veritaserum, Felix felicis, Amortentia and Poly juice potion","Veritaserum, hurnslug, setumaniea and felkamena","Poly juice potion, majoina, conastance and cenputok","Draught of the living death, milliitinie, carnaogdhor and gononala"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, when Harry went to his potions class the first time that year, there were 4 potions on Mr. Slughorns desk. What were they called?","type":"choice","answer":"Veritaserum, Felix felicis, Amortentia and Poly juice potion"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"McLaggen, who was first introduced in Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince hit Harry in the back of his head with a wooden bat.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Was Ron poisoned in the book Harry Potter and the Half-blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Harry almost killed Malfoy.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Is it true that Mrs. Arabella Figg, a character from the Harry Potter books, is a Squib?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, was the horcrux Dumbledore and Harry recovered fake?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Ron","Fred and George","Percy","Harry"],"question":"Who went first into the barrier in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Percy"},{"answers":["Flying with the Cannons","Gold Stars - How do they do it?","Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find them","Quidditch through the ages"],"question":"What was the name of the book which Ron gave Harry for Christmas in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Flying with the Cannons"},{"answers":["bacon","waffles","pancakes","eggs"],"question":"What did Dudley want Harry to pass him at breakfast in chapter 1 of Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"bacon"},{"answers":["Quidditch","The Dueling Club","The Writing on the Wall","The Rogue Bludger"],"question":"What is the title of chapter 11 of the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"The Dueling Club"},{"answers":["scribbling on it","poking holes in it","making finger prints on it","dropping ink blots on it"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, what did Ron keep on doing to his Charms homework?","type":"choice","answer":"dropping ink blots on it"},{"answers":["Sarpensortia","Wingardium Leviosa","Expelliarmus","Rictusempra"],"question":"What was the first spell cast at the dueling match in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Expelliarmus"},{"answers":["Rons","Hermiones","Ginnys","Harrys"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Tom Riddles diary falls into whose hands?","type":"choice","answer":"Ginnys"},{"answers":["Professor Snape","Professor McGonagall","himself","his dad"],"question":"Who does Malfoy want to be headmaster in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Professor Snape"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Does 10 X 10 give 100?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["2","11","4","3"],"question":"How much is 1 + 1?","type":"choice","answer":"2"},{"answers":["9","0","10","7"],"question":"If I have ten apples and I give them all to another person, how many do I have left?","type":"choice","answer":"0"},{"answers":["The steel","The feathers","None of these","They would be equal"],"question":"If you put 1 gram of steel on one scale and 1 gram of feathers on another one, which one would weigh more?","type":"choice","answer":"They would be equal"},{"answers":["$200","$350","$300","$400"],"question":"If Joe had $900 dollars in life savings and he bought a refrigerator for $600 dollars, how much money would he have left?","type":"choice","answer":"$300"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"3.2 are the first numbers in the important mathematical constant pi.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"In mathematics, is a right angle equal to 100 degrees?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["124,416","9999999","0","124,934"],"question":"What is the final result of the following equation: 3 X 6 X 9 X 0 X 12 X 32 X 2 = ?","type":"choice","answer":"0"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"100 multiplied by 0.3 gives 3.00.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Brian","Percival","Roderick","Wulfric"],"question":"Which of these is NOT part of the full name of the fictional character Albus Dumbledore?","type":"choice","answer":"Roderick"},{"answers":["Defense Against the Dark Arts","Transfiguration","Care of Magical Creatures","Potions"],"question":"After graduating from the fictional Hogwarts school, Albus Dumbledore went on to teach this class before becoming headmaster.","type":"choice","answer":"Transfiguration"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"According to the Harry Potter books Albus Dumbledore liked Dementors.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Ring","Diary","Necklace","Sword"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince we find out that Albus Dumbledore destroyed one of Voldemorts horcruxes. In what item was the horcrux contained?","type":"choice","answer":"Ring"},{"answers":["Owl","Phoenix","Demon","Mouse"],"question":"In the Harry Potter series, one of Albus Dumbledores closest friends and companions is Fawkes, a creature that resides in Dumbledores office. What kind of creature is Fawkes?","type":"choice","answer":"Phoenix"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Professor Albus Dumbledores office at the fictional Hogwarts school is protected by a statue of a gargoyle.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Raspberry","Blueberry","Blackberry","Strawberry"],"question":"What is Albus Dumbledores favorite flavor of jam as revealed in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Raspberry"},{"answers":["humid","hot","dry","wet"],"question":"What is the opposite of cold?","type":"choice","answer":"hot"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The opposite of open is closed.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["blue","right","maybe","farm"],"question":"What is the opposite of wrong?","type":"choice","answer":"right"},{"answers":["missing","sad","purple","mad"],"question":"What is the opposite of happy?","type":"choice","answer":"sad"},{"answers":["small","little","huge","miniscule"],"question":"Which of the following words is NOT an opposite of big?","type":"choice","answer":"huge"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"A word with a meaning opposite to that of another word is called a synonym.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The opposite of major is minor.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["top","beside","below","green"],"question":"What is the opposite of above?","type":"choice","answer":"below"},{"answers":["Abbie, Harry","Liiy, Harry","Lilly, James","Abbie, James"],"question":"What were the first names of Harry Potters parents?","type":"choice","answer":"Lilly, James"},{"answers":["Dudley","Ron","George","Fred"],"question":"Which of these characters is Harry Potters best friend?","type":"choice","answer":"Ron"},{"answers":["Sirius, Remus","Malfoy, Neville","Dumbledore, Snape","Malfoy, Snape"],"question":"Which of the following are Harry Potters enemies at school?","type":"choice","answer":"Malfoy, Snape"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Although Harry Potter has a crush on Cho Chang, he ends up with Ginny.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Does Daniel Radcliffe portray Harry Potter?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Albus Dumbledoor","Fred Weasley","Serverus Snape","Horace Slughorn"],"question":"Who was the potions teacher during Harry Potters sixth year at Hogwarts?","type":"choice","answer":"Horace Slughorn"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Fictional character Ron Weasley has male siblings only.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, Professor Binns is a ghost that teaches History of Magic.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Madame Maxime","Mr. Crouch","Ludo Bagman","Rita Skeeter"],"question":"Who accused Hermione of having a thing for famous wizards in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?","type":"choice","answer":"Rita Skeeter"},{"answers":["Tom Voldemort Riddle","Tom Marvolo Riddle","Tom Marvolo Gaunt","Voldemort Tom Riddle"],"question":"What is Lord Voldemorts real name?","type":"choice","answer":"Tom Marvolo Riddle"},{"answers":["Europe","South America","North America","Africa"],"question":"This continent is where Canada, The United States of America, and Mexico are located.","type":"choice","answer":"North America"},{"answers":["Indian","Atlantic","Arctic","Pacific"],"question":"This ocean is bordered by North and South America on the west and Europe and Africa on the east.","type":"choice","answer":"Atlantic"},{"answers":["","","","Crumple Horned Snorkak"],"question":"In the Harry Potter series, Hagrid got kicked out of Hogwarts for possessing what giant creature?","type":"choice","answer":"A giant spider"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, Hagrid was forbidden to use an actual wand. What did he use instead?","type":"choice","answer":"A pink umbrella"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"Hagrid from the Harry Potter series once cared for a creature named Norbert. What was Norbert?","type":"choice","answer":"A dragon"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"In the Harry Potter series Hagrid gets this flying object from Sirius Black and uses it as his main form of transport.","type":"choice","answer":"A motorcycle"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Hagrid dies in the last installment of the Harry Potter series entitled Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Malfoy","Hagrid","Dudley","Ronald"],"question":"What is the name of Harry Potters cousin who often teases and bullies him?","type":"choice","answer":"Dudley"},{"answers":["Pearl","Hermione","Lily","Angel"],"question":"What is the first name of Harry Potters mother?","type":"choice","answer":"Lily"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Professor McGonagall teaches Transfiguration at the fictional Hogwarts school.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The name of Harry Potters owl is Fawkes.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Hermione","Ginny","Penelope","Petunia"],"question":"What is the name of Ronald Weasleys younger sister in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"Ginny"},{"answers":["Professor Sprout","Professor Snape","Professor Dumbledore","Professor McGonagall"],"question":"This professor dislikes Harry Potter and unfairly punishes him while favouring Slytherin students.","type":"choice","answer":"Professor Snape"},{"answers":["Slytherin","Gryffindor","Ravenclaw","Hufflepuffs"],"question":"What is the name of the Hogwarts house where Harry Potter stayed?","type":"choice","answer":"Gryffindor"},{"answers":["Mary and Maria","Al and Ron","Fred and George","Arthur and Artlene"],"question":"What are the names of the famous Weasley twins in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Fred and George"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Harry Potter was the seeker of Gryffindors Quidditch Team.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Norbert","Buckbeak","Twinky","Aragon"],"question":"What is the name of the hippogriff that hurt Draco Malfoy in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"Buckbeak"},{"answers":["Judy Blum","J. K. Rowling","E. B. White","J. R. Rowling"],"question":"Who wrote the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"J. K. Rowling"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"What is the form into which Harry Potters godfather transforms in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"A dog"},{"answers":["Professor Lupin","Professor Moody","Professor Binns","Professor Dumbledore"],"question":"What is the name of the new Defence Against the Dark Arts teacher who first appears in the novel Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"Professor Lupin"},{"answers":["","How to get rid of a boggart","How to sleep without any dreams","The Patronus Charm"],"question":"What did the Defence Against the Dark Arts professor teach Harry after the quidditch match in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"The Patronus Charm"},{"answers":["He uses the marauders invisible cloak.","None of these","He uses only the marauders map.","He uses the marauders map and his invisibility cloak."],"question":"How does Harry Potter go to Hogsmede in the third book of the series?","type":"choice","answer":"He uses the marauders map and his invisibility cloak."},{"answers":["Werewolves","Hippogriffs","Mermaids","Boggarts"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, when Snape taught the Defence Against the Dark Arts, what was the subject the class talked and read about?","type":"choice","answer":"Werewolves"},{"answers":["Time Turner","Hourglass","Changer of Time","Time Stopper"],"question":"What is the device that Hermione uses to travel back in time in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"Time Turner"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Do Harry and Hermione go somewhere, without Ron, at the end of the movie Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["the Queen","the King","the Princes sister","the Prince"],"question":"In Andersens fairy tale The Princess and the Pea, a young woman arrives at the royal familys gate and claims to be a real princess. Who decides to test the validity of her claim by placing a pea under her mattresses?","type":"choice","answer":"the Queen"},{"answers":["their father","the with","their stepfather","their mother"],"question":"Who takes Hansel and Gretel to the forest and abandons them there in Grimms classic fairy tale?","type":"choice","answer":"their father"},{"answers":["The Snow Queen","All of these","The Little Match Girl","The Little Mermaid"],"question":"Which of these fairy tales by Danish author Hans Christian Andersen has a happy ending?","type":"choice","answer":"The Snow Queen"},{"answers":["Beauty and the Beast","King Thrushbeard","Rumpelstiltskin","Bluebeard"],"question":"In what fairy tale does a curious wife find the dead bodies of her husbands previous wives?","type":"choice","answer":"Bluebeard"},{"answers":["a pig","a rooster","a cat","a donkey"],"question":"In the fairy tale The Musicians of Bremen, four animals decide to become musicians upon finding that they are no longer useful to their owners. Which of the following is not one of the four animals?","type":"choice","answer":"a pig"},{"answers":["Aladdin - a lamp","The Little Mermaid - a key with drops of blood on it","Snow White  - a mirror","The Wild Swans - nettle shirts"],"question":"Which magic object is not correctly matched with the fairy tale?","type":"choice","answer":"The Little Mermaid - a key with drops of blood on it"},{"answers":["Rapunzel","Sleeping Beauty","The Emperors New Clothes","The Wolf and the Seven Young Kids"],"question":"What popular fairy tale is not a recorded folktale, but an original work?","type":"choice","answer":"The Emperors New Clothes"},{"answers":["because she picked up a flower from the Beasts garden","because her sisters have stolen an enchanted mirror and a ring from the Beast","because her father picked up a flower from the Beasts garden","because her sisters have stolen jewelry from the Beast"],"question":"Why does Belle have to live in the castle with the Beast in the fairy tale The Beauty and the Beast?","type":"choice","answer":"because her father picked up a flower from the Beasts garden"},{"answers":["The Princess is named Aurora, the Prince is anonymous.","Briar-Rose and Stefan","Aurora and Philip","They are anonymous."],"question":"What are the names of the Princess and the Prince in the 1959 Disney animated feature, based on Charles Perrault classic tale Sleeping Beauty?","type":"choice","answer":"Aurora and Philip"},{"answers":["Tom Thumb","The Steadfast Tin Soldier","Hop o My Thumb","Thumbelina"],"question":"What diminutive fairy tale character encounters a toad, a beetle, a mouse, a mole and a swallow?","type":"choice","answer":"Thumbelina"},{"answers":["20","17","19","16"],"question":"Joe has 20 apples. He gave 2 away to a friend and then he ate one. How many apples did he have after that?","type":"choice","answer":"17"},{"answers":["8","2","6","4"],"question":"What does x equal in this equation?\r","type":"choice","answer":"2"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Can 37 be divided into 2 evenly?","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["5","0","10","2"],"question":"What is the answer to the following:\r","type":"choice","answer":"5"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The reciprocal of 3/4 is 1 1/3.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["10","11","12","13"],"question":"What is the square root of 121?","type":"choice","answer":"11"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Is this correct?\r","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["37","27","207","17"],"question":"One angle in a triangle is 47 degrees and the second angle is 106 degrees. How many degrees are in the third angle?","type":"choice","answer":"27"},{"answers":["16","17","15","14"],"question":"What is the missing number?\r","type":"choice","answer":"16"},{"answers":["4","5","7","6"],"question":"You have a right-angled triangle. You know that one leg is 3 cm long and the second leg is 4 cm long. What is the length of the hypotenuse of that triangle?","type":"choice","answer":"5"},{"answers":["Jamestown in present day Virginia","Boston in present day Massachusetts","Providence in what is present day Rhode Island","Charlestown in present day South Carolina"],"question":"Founded in 1607, this was the first successful English settlement in what is now the United States.","type":"choice","answer":"Jamestown in present day Virginia"},{"answers":["Holland","France","Germany","Spain"],"question":"Up until 1763, the English and this other European nation fought a series of wars and smaller conflicts to see who would dominate what is now the US and Canada.","type":"choice","answer":"France"},{"answers":["whether the English Parliament or colonial assemblies would control taxes in the colonies","religious differences between American colonists and Britain","restrictions on the number of English persons who could move to the English colonies","disagreements between Parliament and the colonies over relations with the Native Americans (Indians)"],"question":"What was the biggest issue that eventually led to the English colonies rebellion against their mother country and sparked the American Revolutionary War?","type":"choice","answer":"whether the English Parliament or colonial assemblies would control taxes in the colonies"},{"answers":["all of these","He was the first president of the United States.","He was a successful Virginia plantation owner.","He was commander of the American Continental Army during the Revolutionary War."],"question":"Which of these statements about George Washington is true?","type":"choice","answer":"all of these"},{"answers":["Yorktown","Lexington","Boston","Saratoga"],"question":"The final victory in the American Revolutionary War which convinced the British to grant independence to their former colonies was a victory won by combined French and American forces at this place.","type":"choice","answer":"Yorktown"},{"answers":["James Polk","Andrew Jackson","Thomas Jefferson","John Adams"],"question":"The seventh president of the United States was the first US president elected from a state west of the Appalachian Mountains (Tennessee). He was also the leader of the US forces who gained a major victory over the British at New Orleans in the War of 1812. Who was he?","type":"choice","answer":"Andrew Jackson"},{"answers":["Oregon","Arizona","California","Nevada"],"question":"As a result of victory in the Mexican War of 1846-48, the United States gained all of the following states EXCEPT this one.","type":"choice","answer":"Oregon"},{"answers":["slavery","status of new western territories","states rights","tariffs"],"question":"What was the one irreconcilable issue between North and South that led to the American Civil War?","type":"choice","answer":"slavery"},{"answers":["Gettysburg","Shiloh","Second Bull Run","Antietam"],"question":"The Union victory in this battle, fought in July 1863, is generally considered the turning point of the American Civil War. After the battle President Lincoln made a memorable speech at the site of the battle. What was the battle?","type":"choice","answer":"Gettysburg"},{"answers":["Blacks in the southern states were integrated into the southern population with very little conflict or discrimination.","Native Americans (Indians) were generally treated fairly and territorial disputes were settled.","US industrialization advanced rapidly.","Laws were passed that greatly restricted European immigration into the US."],"question":"Which of the following is true about the United States in the period between the end of the Civil War in 1865 and the beginning of the 20th century?","type":"choice","answer":"US industrialization advanced rapidly."},{"answers":["German submarines began sinking US ships in 1917.","The US had strong cultural and commercial ties with Britain and France.","France and Britain were democratic and Germany was not.","President Wilson wanted to destroy communism."],"question":"Which of the following was NOT a reason why the US entered World War One on the side of Britain and France?","type":"choice","answer":"President Wilson wanted to destroy communism."},{"answers":["US joining any international organization","alcoholic beverages","prostitution","same sex marriages"],"question":"In 1919 an amendment to the US Constitution (which was rescinded in 1933) prohibited which of the following?","type":"choice","answer":"alcoholic beverages"},{"answers":["Programs to provide jobs by building roads, schools, dams, etc.","The Securities and Exchange Commission to regulate the stock market","Social Security that provided pensions for retired workers","All of these"],"question":"In 1933 Franklin Roosevelt was elected president. He promised to bring a New Deal to Americans to bring recovery from the Great Depression and improve social conditions. Which of the following did his New Deal include?","type":"choice","answer":"All of these"},{"answers":["Leyte Gulf","Okinawa","Singapore","Midway"],"question":"The Japanese defeat in this naval battle in the Pacific is generally considered to be the turning point of the Second World War.","type":"choice","answer":"Midway"},{"answers":["There was never any actual warfare in the Cold War.","It was partly a clash of very different ideologies.","It began soon after World War Two ended, partly because of Soviet domination of Eastern Europe.","Nuclear weapons were a threat to both sides in the Cold War."],"question":"Which of these statements is NOT true about the Cold War?","type":"choice","answer":"There was never any actual warfare in the Cold War."},{"answers":["Germany","North Korea","China","Cuba"],"question":"Many think that the closest the world came to nuclear war was in 1962 when President Kennedy demanded that the Soviets remove nuclear missiles they had recently placed in this country.","type":"choice","answer":"Cuba"},{"answers":["1939","1932","1934","1927"],"question":"Ole Kirk Christiansen, the founder of the LEGO Group, started producing wooden toys in what year?","type":"choice","answer":"1932"},{"answers":["Put Together","Play Well","Build Well","Stack Well"],"question":"In 1934, Ole Kirk Christiansen named his toy-producing company LEGO, a word derived from the Danish phrase leg godt, which means what in English?","type":"choice","answer":"Play Well"},{"answers":["1945","1944","1942","1940"],"question":"During this year the Lego company, founded by Ole Kirk Christiansen, was devastated by a fire.","type":"choice","answer":"1942"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"LEGO was the first company in Denmark to buy and use a plastic injection-molding machine for toys.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["1952","1949","1950","1947"],"question":"In what year did Godtfred Kirk Christiansen become Junior Vice President of the LEGO company?","type":"choice","answer":"1950"},{"answers":["LEGO Building Set","LEGO Toy Set of Building","LEGO System of Play","LEGO System"],"question":"What is the name of the revolutionary LEGO series of 28 sets and 8 vehicles, launched in 1955?","type":"choice","answer":"LEGO System of Play"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In 1963, the LEGO company replaced the building substance for the bricks, cellulose acetate with acrylonitrile butadiene stryrene, which improved the color quality.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In 1989, the LEGO company released a new series, named Pirates.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Ravenclaw","Gryffindor","Slytherin","Hufflepuff"],"question":"Which house of Hogwarts was fictional character Sirius Black in when he attended the famous school?","type":"choice","answer":"Gryffindor"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"Harry Potter character Sirius Black was an Animagi meaning that he could take the form of an animal. What animal could he emulate?","type":"choice","answer":"A dog"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix the headquarters of the organization was in Sirius family home.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Harry Potter and The Sorcerers Stone","Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban","Harry potter and The Chamber of Secrets","Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows"],"question":"In which Harry Potter novel did Sirius Black make his first major appearance?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"What magical flying item of Sirius Black was given to Hagrid upon the knowledge of Harry Potters parents death?","type":"choice","answer":"A motorcycle"},{"answers":["Orion","Teodor","Draco","Rudolph"],"question":"What was the name of Sirius Blacks father in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Orion"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Sirius Black dies in the novel Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Divination","Potions","Charms","Astronomy"],"question":"Which of the following classes was taught by Professor Snape in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Potions"},{"answers":["He was half muggle.","He killed Albus Dumbledore.","He was in love with Harrys mother.","He was Lord Voldemorts brother."],"question":"What secret about Professor Snape was divulged in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, which is the final book in the series?","type":"choice","answer":"He was in love with Harrys mother."},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the Harry Potter series, Professor Snape became headmaster of Hogwarts after the death of Dumbledore.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Doe","Dragon","Wolf","Snake"],"question":"What was Snapes patronus in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Doe"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the final book of the Harry Potter series, Harry finally kills Snape.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Care of magical Creatures","Potions","Divination","Defense Against the Dark Arts"],"question":"In the Harry Potter series, what was the teaching position most coveted by Professor Snape?","type":"choice","answer":"Defense Against the Dark Arts"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the final book in the Harry Potter series, it is revealed that Harry names one of his sons after Snape.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Is fictional character Snape the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Rainlet","Cloudy boy","Weatherboy","Weatherby"],"question":"What did Mr. Crouch from the Ministry of Magic call Percy in book 4 of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Weatherby"},{"answers":["Professor Snape","Professor Sprout","Professor Quirrell","Professor Flitwick"],"question":"There were all types of enchantments guarding the Sorcerers Stone. Which teacher put the flying keys there to protect it in the first Harry Potter book?","type":"choice","answer":"Professor Flitwick"},{"answers":["Books 3 and 5","Books 3 and 4","Books 4 and 5","Books 3 and 6"],"question":"In which two books did Harry Potter make a Patronus because he thought he saw a dementor, even though it was not really a dementor?","type":"choice","answer":"Books 3 and 4"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the sixth book of the Harry Potter series, Professor Slughorn became the Head of Slytherin.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The character of Sirius Black is mentioned in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban for the first time.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Tom Riddle","Harry Potter","Pansy Parkinson","Ron Weasley"],"question":"Which of the following Harry Potter characters is not a prefect?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter"},{"answers":["Cho","No one","Ginny","Hermione"],"question":"Which of these characters does Harry kiss in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Ginny"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Lavender Brown and Ron Won Won Weasley start going out in chapter 9 of Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Kingsley Shackelbolt","Stubby Boardman","Percival Wulfricshire","Amelia Bones"],"question":"What previously mentioned character was killed in chapter 1 of Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Amelia Bones"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Cho Chang waves to Harry once but then hurries away with Marietta.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["","","An imperious curse",""],"question":"What does Merope supposedly use to make Tom Riddle Sr. fall in love with her in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"A love potion"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, is Dumbledores blood the only blood used in the Cavern by the sea where the Horcrux is hidden?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Inferi","Infery","Infreri","Infrery"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, a corpse that is re-animated but isn’t alive is called what?","type":"choice","answer":"Inferi"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Harry destroyed two Horcruxes in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Snakes","Wolves","Spiders","Centaurs"],"question":"Lord Voldemort had the ability to talk to these creatures.","type":"choice","answer":"Snakes"},{"answers":["John","Michael","Tom","Ron"],"question":"What is Lord Voldemorts real first name?","type":"choice","answer":"Tom"},{"answers":["Sword","Stone","Diary","Ring"],"question":"What was the very first of Lord Voldemorts horcruxes to appear in the Harry Potter series of books?","type":"choice","answer":"Diary"},{"answers":["Ravenclaw","Huffelpuff","Slytherin","Gryffendore"],"question":"Which of these Hogwarts founders was Lord Voldemorts ancestor?","type":"choice","answer":"Slytherin"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Lord Voldemort is related to Harry Potter.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Tonks","Severus Snape","Hagrid","Professor Lupin"],"question":"Which of these characters does Voldemort NOT kill in the final Harry Potter book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"Hagrid"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Harry Potter defeats and kills Lord Voldemort in the final Harry Potter book.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Alices Adventures in Wonderland","Peter and Wendy","Pinocchio","Pippi Longstocking"],"question":"What childrens novel features Neverland, the magical island where people cease to age?","type":"choice","answer":"Peter and Wendy"},{"answers":["Both of these","Pinocchio","None of these","Buratino"],"question":"What classic fictional character is a long-nosed wooden puppet?","type":"choice","answer":"Both of these"},{"answers":["the Queen of Hearts","the Mock Turtle","the March Hare","the Chief Weasel"],"question":"Which of the following is not a character from Lewis Carrolls 1865 novel Alices Adventures in Wonderland?","type":"choice","answer":"the Chief Weasel"},{"answers":["the Fox","the Snake","the Lamplighter","the Rose"],"question":"What character from Antoine de Saint-Exupérys novella, The Little Prince, utters these famous lines that sum up the essence of the book: One cannot see well except with the heart, the essential is invisible to the eyes.?","type":"choice","answer":"the Fox"},{"answers":["Theodor Seuss Geisel","Helen Beatrix Potter","Madonna Louise Ciccone","Dorothy Gladys Smith"],"question":"What is the birth name of the author who penned The English Roses, a childrens book that follows the lives of four girls?","type":"choice","answer":"Madonna Louise Ciccone"},{"answers":["C. S. Lewis","Lemony Snicket","A. A. Milne","Lewis Carroll"],"question":"What childrens book author named one of his central characters after his son?","type":"choice","answer":"A. A. Milne"},{"answers":["One Hundred and One Dalmatians","The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh","Mulan","Bambi"],"question":"Which of these Disney animated features is not based on a book written by an European author?","type":"choice","answer":"Mulan"},{"answers":["Little House in the Big Woods","Anne of Green Gables","Little Women","Heidi"],"question":"What best-selling novel tells the story of an orphan girl adopted by middle-aged siblings, Marilla and Matthew Cuthbert?","type":"choice","answer":"Anne of Green Gables"},{"answers":["Karlsson","Pippi","Ronia","Lucy Pevensie"],"question":"This extraordinary strong, red-haired fictional character lives in Villa Villekula with a monkey, named Mr. Nilsson.","type":"choice","answer":"Pippi"},{"answers":["Lucy Pevensie, Caspian - C. S. Lewis","Mowgly, Raksha - Edgar Rice Burroughs","Joe Harper, Becky Thatcher  - Mark Twain","Meg March, Amy March - Louisa May Alcott"],"question":"Which characters are not correctly matched with the authors who created them?","type":"choice","answer":"Mowgly, Raksha - Edgar Rice Burroughs"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Severus Snape was headmaster for a period of time.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["He discovered something important.","He forgot what time it was.","He does not like meetings.","He was teaching."],"question":"In the first chapter of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, why was Snape late for a meeting with Lord Voldemort?","type":"choice","answer":"He discovered something important."},{"answers":["Harry got cut by a fragment of a mirror.","Dudley put a cup of tea right behind Harrys door and Harry stepped on it.","Dudley put a glass of water behind Harrys door and Harry stepped on it.","Harry bit his lip."],"question":"The first sentence in the second chapter in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows is Harry was bleeding. Why is that so?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry got cut by a fragment of a mirror."},{"answers":["Resurrection Stone","Magical Mirror","Elder Wand","Invisibility Cloak"],"question":"Which of the following is NOT a Deathly Hallow?","type":"choice","answer":"Magical Mirror"},{"answers":["Ron","Fred","Bill","George"],"question":"Which Weasley boy got his ear cut off in the last book of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"George"},{"answers":["Dudley Dursley","Vernon Dursley","Dudley Vernon","Vernon Dudley"],"question":"What did Harry Potter say that his name was when he, Ron, and Hermione got caught by a gang of Snatchers in Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"Vernon Dudley"},{"answers":["6","8","5","7"],"question":"If you add 3 to 5, what would be the result?","type":"choice","answer":"8"},{"answers":["$2.25","$1.50","$1.00","$2.00"],"question":"If Jane had $3.00 and went to the store and bought a yo yo for $1.00, how much would Jane have left?","type":"choice","answer":"$2.00"},{"answers":["14","15","13","16"],"question":"What is the correct solution to this problem: 16 - 4 + 3 =?","type":"choice","answer":"15"},{"answers":["8 dollars","3 dollars","7 dollars","5 dollars"],"question":"If T.J. went to the circus with 10 dollars and bought some fruit snacks for 3 dollars, how much money would T. J. then have left over?","type":"choice","answer":"7 dollars"},{"answers":["5 dollars","10 dollars","8 dollars","15 dollars"],"question":"If Lindsay had $20.00 and bought 3 tickets to the Mets game, how much money would Lindsay have left if each ticket cost 5 dollars?","type":"choice","answer":"5 dollars"},{"answers":["3","4","2","1"],"question":"If Donna bought 5 blowpop lollipops from the candy store and gave her friend 2 of them, how many blowpops would Donna then have?","type":"choice","answer":"3"},{"answers":["12","6","18","10"],"question":"How many inches are there in a foot?","type":"choice","answer":"12"},{"answers":["14","13","12","11"],"question":"If Anthony had 8 apples, 2 oranges and 3 pears, how many pieces of fruit does Anthony have altogether?","type":"choice","answer":"13"},{"answers":["8","9","7","6"],"question":"What is the solution to this problem 12-3=?","type":"choice","answer":"9"},{"answers":["40 dollars","6 dollars","4 dollars","5 dollars"],"question":"Amanda went to the book store to buy some books. Her mom gave her a $10 bill. She bought two books that cost $2.00 each and a bookmark that cost $1.00. How much change did Amanda give her mother when she got home?","type":"choice","answer":"5 dollars"},{"answers":["None of these","He was able to contact his cousin Bellatrix who helped him escape from Azkaban.","He transformed into a dog.","He was able to control one of the dementors."],"question":"How did Sirius Black escape from Azkaban, the wizard prison in the third book of the Harry Poter series?","type":"choice","answer":"He transformed into a dog."},{"answers":["Severus Snape","Remus Lupin","Dolores Umbridge","Alastor Mad-Eye Moody"],"question":"Who is the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in Harry Potters third year at Hogwarts?","type":"choice","answer":"Remus Lupin"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Fictional character Remus Lupin was an animagus.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Expelliarmus","Impedimenta","Wingardium Leviosa","Expecto Patronum"],"question":"What is the spell incantation for conjuring a Patronus in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"Expecto Patronum"},{"answers":["Care of Magical Creatures","Potions","Transfiguration","Defense Against the Dark Arts"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, Rubeus Hagrid was appointed by Headmaster Albus Dumbledore as the new teacher of what subject?","type":"choice","answer":"Care of Magical Creatures"},{"answers":["Fred and George","Remus Lupin","Argus Filch","Rubeus Hagrid"],"question":"Who gave the Marauders Map to Harry in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?","type":"choice","answer":"Fred and George"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The Shrieking Shack, depicted in the Harry Potter books, was considered to be the most haunted place in Great Britain.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Even without a permission slip, Harry Potter was able to go to Hogsmeade with Ron and Hermione during certain weekends.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Nikki DeLoach","Britney Spears","Justin Timberlake","J"],"question":"In 2000, this Mouseketeer became the youngest person to be both host and musical guest on Saturday Night Live.","type":"choice","answer":"Britney Spears"},{"answers":["The Party","Spin and Marty","Emerald Cove","The Hardy Boys"],"question":"Name the weekly ten-minute drama on the All-New Mickey Mouse Club starring Tony Lucca, Keri Russel and JC Chasez?","type":"choice","answer":"Emerald Cove"},{"answers":["An oil painting","Amelia Bones","None of these","Herbert Chorley"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, who delivered the Prime Minister the message that the Minister of Magic had sent?","type":"choice","answer":"An oil painting"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, The Minister of Magic came only once to visit the Prime Minister.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Pumpkin juice","Dragon blood","Dwarf blood","Ink"],"question":"What was spattered over the wallpaper on Professor Slughorns house in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Dragon blood"},{"answers":["Luna Lovegood","Luna Lovegoods uncle","Ron Weasley","Luna Lovegoods father"],"question":"Who wrote the magazine named Quibbler in the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Luna Lovegoods father"},{"answers":["Alohomora","Sectumsempra","None of these","Felix Felicis"],"question":"What was the name of spell that Harry used on Malfoy in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Sectumsempra"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Do Hermione and Ron secretly like each other in the sixth book of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Harry - Ginny","Harry - Hermione","Harry - Cho","None of these"],"question":"In the sixth book of the Harry Potter series, which of the following characters eventually formed a couple?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry - Ginny"},{"answers":["blue","purple","red","black"],"question":"What color was Quirrels turban in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"purple"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Harry Potters middle name is James.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["So Harry and Ron would have something to run into with the flying car","The students could have shade","So Lupin could come to school","To protect the school"],"question":"Why was the womping willow planted in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"So Lupin could come to school"},{"answers":["He was the only candidate.","He was actually good enough.","His father bought brooms for the whole team","He shot a man in Reno just to watch him die."],"question":"How does Malfoy join the Slytherin quidditch team?","type":"choice","answer":"His father bought brooms for the whole team"},{"answers":["He is Harrys Godfather.","He is Harrys uncle.","He is Harrys cousin.","He is Harrys half-brother."],"question":"How is Sirius related to Harry Potter?","type":"choice","answer":"He is Harrys Godfather."},{"answers":["Lupin","Trelawny","McGonagall","Snape"],"question":"Who is the teacher in the Harry Potter books that is made fun of by the Marauders map?","type":"choice","answer":"Snape"},{"answers":["J.R. Rowling","C.S. Lewis","J.K. Rowling","J.R. Tolkien"],"question":"Who wrote the Harry Potter series of books?","type":"choice","answer":"J.K. Rowling"},{"answers":["Swan and Otter","Stag and Frog","Frog and Otter","Frog and Swan"],"question":"What were Hermiones and Chos patronus forms in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"Swan and Otter"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Fictional characters Ron Weasley and Harry Potter met on the Hogwarts Express.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Every headmaster/headmistress of the fictional Hogwarts school has had the same office.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["antidote to love potions","wand","bezoar","boggart"],"question":"What magical object did Harry Potter use to save Ron from poisoning?","type":"choice","answer":"bezoar"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Fictional character Mr. Weasley was on guard duty when the basilisk attacked him.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Does fictional character Ron Weasley live at 12, Grimmauld Place?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince","Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.","Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban","Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets"],"question":"In what Harry Potter book did the Brockdale Bridge collapse?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Fictional characters Fred and George Weasley get kicked out of Hogwarts.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Phineas Nigeallus","Minevera McGonagall","Severus Snape","Albus Dumbledore"],"question":"Who is Headmaster at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in books 1-6 of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Albus Dumbledore"},{"answers":["Snape","McGonagall","Lupin","Trelawney"],"question":"Who is head of the fictional Gryffindor house?","type":"choice","answer":"McGonagall"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Fictional character Professor Snape is head of Ravenclaw house.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Is Flitwick head of Huffllepuff house in the Harry Potter series of books?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Slughorn","McGonagal","Sprout","Snape"],"question":"Who is head of Slytherin house in the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"Slughorn"},{"answers":["Sprout","The Bloody Baron","The Gray Lady","Flitwick"],"question":"Who is the ghost of Ravenclaw in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"The Gray Lady"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Professor Sprout is head of Hufflepuff, one of the fictional Hogwarts houses.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Moaning Myrtle","The Gray Lady","The Bloody Baron","Nearly Headless Nick"],"question":"Who is the Gryffindor ghost in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"Nearly Headless Nick"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, the Bloody Baron is Slytherins ghost.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Is Harry Potter a member of Gryffindor house?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["12","7","14","71"],"question":"What is the square root of 144?","type":"choice","answer":"12"},{"answers":["Keys, Devils Snare, chessboard, potions","Chessboard, keys, Devils Snare, potions","Devils Snare, chessboard, keys, potions","Devils Snare, keys, chessboard, potions"],"question":"In the first book of the Harry Potter series, when Harry, Ron and Hermione went into the restricted corridor, what was the order of the obstacles to get to Quirrell?","type":"choice","answer":"Devils Snare, keys, chessboard, potions"},{"answers":["a Dachshund","a black dog","a black cat","a yellow cat"],"question":"What shape does Sirius Blacks Animagus take in the 3rd book of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"a black dog"},{"answers":["number 19, Grimmauld place","number 15, Grimmauld place","number 13, Grimmauld place","number 12, Grimmauld place"],"question":"What is the address of the Order of the Phoenix headquarters in the Harry Potter novels?","type":"choice","answer":"number 12, Grimmauld place"},{"answers":["an ordinary house","an run-down shack","a school bus","an orphanage"],"question":"Where did fictional character Tom Riddle (Voldemort) live before going to live and study at Hogwarts?","type":"choice","answer":"an orphanage"},{"answers":["51","53","54","55"],"question":"How many people died at the fictional battle of Hogwarts?","type":"choice","answer":"54"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Did Harry Potter marry Ginny Weasley?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"All the books of the Harry Potter series are set in England and Scotland.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["1","3","2","4"],"question":"How many champions names came out of the fictional Goblet of Fire?","type":"choice","answer":"4"},{"answers":["Madam Lulu.","Aunt Josephine","Esme Squalor","Count Olaf"],"question":"Who was the first guardian to whom the Baudelaires were sent in A Series of Unfortunate Events?","type":"choice","answer":"Count Olaf"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the novel The Penultimate Peril, Jaques Snicket was one of the two people who signed into the hotel as J.S..","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Hector","Jerome Squalor","Uncle Monty","Esme Squalor"],"question":"Which character from A Series of Unfortunate Events said that orphans were in?","type":"choice","answer":"Esme Squalor"},{"answers":["The King of Arizona","The President of Nepal","The Prime Minister of New York","The Grand Admiral of Canada"],"question":"Which of the following were mentioned in the book The Ersatz Elevator?","type":"choice","answer":"The King of Arizona"},{"answers":["Uncle Monty","Duncan Quagmire","Kit Snicket","Isadora Quagmire"],"question":"Which of the following fictional characters, depicted by Lemony Snicket, is a poet?","type":"choice","answer":"Isadora Quagmire"},{"answers":["Phils","Beatrices","Carmelita Spats","Sirs"],"question":"In A Series of Unfortunate Events, whose head was always hidden behind a cloud of smoke?","type":"choice","answer":"Sirs"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"In the second book of A Series of Unfortunate Events, did Count Olaf trick the Baudelaires into thinking he was really Stephano?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["The Miserable Mill","The Bad Beginning","The Vile Village","The Penultimate Peril"],"question":"In which of Lemony Snickets books does Jaques Snicket die?","type":"choice","answer":"The Vile Village"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In A Series of Unfortunate Events, Klaus was the best inventor out of all the Baudelaires.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Willard","Wanker","Hank","Wubbzy"],"question":"This character is in a show with his two friends, Widget and Walden. He is yellow with a long, springy tail, and greets people by saying, Wow wow.","type":"choice","answer":"Wubbzy"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The show Dora the Explorer features a little girl who goes on all sorts of adventures with her friend, Tico the Dog.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Yo Pinky Dinky!","Yo Diddle Diddle","Yo Mama Jama","Yo Gabba Gabba!"],"question":"This show features characters with offbeat names like Muno, Foofa, Brobee, Toodee, Plex, and DJ Lance.","type":"choice","answer":"Yo Gabba Gabba!"},{"answers":["Pearl","Fluff","Louise","Ruby"],"question":"A TV show that debuted in 2002 features 2 bunnies. Max is a 3 year-old bunny that is always doing something to distract his sister, although he always manages to help her in the end. What is his sisters name?","type":"choice","answer":"Ruby"},{"answers":["Sleepy Town","Lazy Town","Active Town","Funky Town"],"question":"This show features an active hero named Sportacus, who uses exercise and good nutrition to thwart the schemes of the slothful Robbie Rotten. Most of the characters in this show are puppets.","type":"choice","answer":"Lazy Town"},{"answers":["Stan and Stu","Steve and Joe","Larry and Jake","Jack and Jim"],"question":"The show Blues Clues featured 2 different hosts during its run. What were their names?","type":"choice","answer":"Steve and Joe"},{"answers":["The Backyardamals","The Backyardigans","The Backyard Gang","The Backyard Band"],"question":"This show follows Pablo the Penguin, Tyrone the Moose, Tasha the Hippopotamus, Austin the Kangaroo, and Uniqua on their imaginary adventures in the backyard.","type":"choice","answer":"The Backyardigans"},{"answers":["Ni Hao, Kai-Lan","Ni Hao, Karen Chau","Ni Hao, Yeoh-La","Ni Hao, Shu-Shu"],"question":"This show centers around a young girl, who speaks English and Chinese, and teaches problem solving. Other characters featured on the show are the girls grandfather,  Ye Ye, and her friends Rintoo, Tolee, Hoho, and Lulu.","type":"choice","answer":"Ni Hao, Kai-Lan"},{"answers":["The Teamwork Trio","The Super Squirrels","The Wonder Pets","The Amazing Animals"],"question":"Linny, Tuck, and Ming MIng too! These schoolhouse animals are always using teamwork to save baby animals in trouble.","type":"choice","answer":"The Wonder Pets"},{"answers":["Marco","Diego","Juan","Luis"],"question":"This young boy started off in his cousin Dora the Explorers show, but soon received his own show. He is an animal rescuer, along with his sister, Alicia.","type":"choice","answer":"Diego"},{"answers":["Educational High School","Experiment House","English School for Grammar","Experimentation Hall"],"question":"In The Silver Chair, Eustace Scrubb returns to Narnia with his schoolmate Jill Pole, who attends what school with him?","type":"choice","answer":"Experiment House"},{"answers":["Jill gives him a hug","He looses his balance and falls","He is attacked by a lion","Nothing"],"question":"What happens to Eustace as a result of Jills showing off at the edge of the cliff in the book The Silver Chair?","type":"choice","answer":"He looses his balance and falls"},{"answers":["To kill the evil Green Witch, who has terrorized Narnia for a decade","To prevent an attack from the underworld upon Narnia","To free the talking beasts of Narnia from the tyranny of the Giants","To find the Prince Rilian, who has been missing for ten years"],"question":"In the novel The Silver Chair, Aslan gives Jill and Eustace a task and four signs to help them find the way. What is the task?","type":"choice","answer":"To find the Prince Rilian, who has been missing for ten years"},{"answers":["Reepicheep","Edmund","Drinian","Caspian"],"question":"The first of the signs given to Jill by Aslan in The Silver Chair was that Eustace was to see an old friend. Who did that old friend turn out to be?","type":"choice","answer":"Caspian"},{"answers":["Parakeet","Gryphon","Owl","Eagle"],"question":"What sort of creature is Glimfeather, who helps Eustace and Jill get started on their journey in The Silver Chair?","type":"choice","answer":"Owl"},{"answers":["He is an optimist and is usually proved wrong","He is an optimist, but is usually proved right","He is a pessimist and is usually proved right","He is a pessimist, but is usually proved wrong"],"question":"Which of the following statements most correctly describes Puddleglum the Marsh-Wiggles outlook on life in C.S. Lewiss book The Silver Chair?","type":"choice","answer":"He is a pessimist, but is usually proved wrong"},{"answers":["They are captured by the Giants and thrown into cages.","They are turned away by the Giants that live there and forced to sleep out in the cold.","Nobody answers.","They are allowed entry and are given food, warm drink and beds."],"question":"What happens to Eustace, Jill and Puddleglum in The Silver Chair, when they knock on the gate of the Giant city of Harfang?","type":"choice","answer":"They are allowed entry and are given food, warm drink and beds."},{"answers":["Have Faith","Trust Me","Never Surrender","Under Me"],"question":"In The Silver Chair, Jill has a dream in which she sees what two words out of the window of her room?","type":"choice","answer":"Under Me"},{"answers":["Father Christmas","Father Time","Mother Earth","Mother Nature"],"question":"When Jill, Eustace and Puddleglum reach the Underworld, in The Silver Chair, they pass a large person sleeping and are told that this is who?","type":"choice","answer":"Father Time"},{"answers":["He forgets who he is and goes on a murderous rampage","He enters the world of dreams and comes back with ingredients for the Witchs potions","He relives the death of his mother through the eyes of the serpent that killed her","He remembers who he is and must be tied to a Silver Chair to prevent his escape"],"question":"In The Silver Chair, Prince Rilian is found to be under the enchantment of the Green Witch.  What happens to Rilian for one hour each night under the Witchs spell?","type":"choice","answer":"He remembers who he is and must be tied to a Silver Chair to prevent his escape"},{"answers":["in the name of the White Witch","in the name of God","in the name of Aslan","in the name of the Green Witch"],"question":"In the Silver Chair, Eustace, Jill and Puddleglum rescue Rilian from the Silver Chair after he begs them to do it in whose name?","type":"choice","answer":"in the name of Aslan"},{"answers":["Prince Rilian","Eustace","Jill","Puddleglum"],"question":"Which character in The Silver Chair burns his foot while putting out a magical fire created by the Green Witch?","type":"choice","answer":"Puddleglum"},{"answers":["Unicorn","Gryphon","Centaur","Pegasus"],"question":"In The Silver Chair, Jill and Eustace are allowed the privilege to ride what creature, which is most often too proud to be ridden?","type":"choice","answer":"Centaur"},{"answers":["Aslan","Rilian","Caspian","Puddleglum"],"question":"Which character from the book The Silver Chair accompanies Jill and Eustace back to their own world when Aslan sends them out of his country?","type":"choice","answer":"Caspian"},{"answers":["Daniel Fancliff","Daniel Radcliffe","None of these","Wayne Knight"],"question":"What is the name of the actor who portrayed Harry Potter?","type":"choice","answer":"Daniel Radcliffe"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Cho Chang was Harry Potters girlfriend.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Professor Snape","None of these","Professor Lupin","Professor Umbridge"],"question":"What was the name of the DADA teacher in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"None of these"},{"answers":["none of these","Potterwatch","The Daily Prophet","The Quibler"],"question":"What is the name of the anti-Ministry of Magic radio station in Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"Potterwatch"},{"answers":["6","4","7","5"],"question":"How many books are in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"7"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Did Harry Potters parents die on Halloween?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["none of these","He didnt work.","minister of magic","quidditch player"],"question":"What was the job of Harry Potters dad?","type":"choice","answer":"He didnt work."},{"answers":["Nephew","Uncle","Cousin","Brother"],"question":"In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Lucy and Edmund Pevensie return to Narnia along with a boy named Eustace. What relation is Eustace to Lucy and Edmund?","type":"choice","answer":"Cousin"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, the three children travel to Narnia by what magical object?","type":"choice","answer":"A painting"},{"answers":["","Queen Susans horn","Seven Lords of Narnia banished by Caspians uncle, Miraz","Five Rings of Power created by Aslan"],"question":"In the third book of the Chronicles of Narnia, the three children are rescued from the sea by Caspian and the crew of the Dawn Treader, who are on a voyage east from Narnia to find what?","type":"choice","answer":"Seven Lords of Narnia banished by Caspians uncle, Miraz"},{"answers":["Kicking him into the water","Stealing his ration of cheese","Swinging him around by his tail","Insulting the honor of his mother"],"question":"At the beginning of the voyage, depicted in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Eustace is a nuisance to all aboard the Dawn Treader, including Reepicheep the mouse, whom he greatly offends by doing what?","type":"choice","answer":"Swinging him around by his tail"},{"answers":["Castaways","Pirates","Ghosts","Slave Traders"],"question":"While walking across the island of Felimath, featured in the book The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Caspian, Reepicheep and the three children come across a band of men who they discover to be what?","type":"choice","answer":"Slave Traders"},{"answers":["Tapwater Island","Clearwater Island","Goldwater Island","Deathwater Island"],"question":"What name do the voyagers in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader give to the island on which they find the armor and sword of Lord Restimar lying beside a small pool of clear water?","type":"choice","answer":"Deathwater Island"},{"answers":["They had only one foot","They had only one eye","They had only one nostril","They had only one hand"],"question":"The Duffers, described in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, have made themselves invisible and wish Lucy to help them become visible again. What was strange about the Duffers?","type":"choice","answer":"They had only one foot"},{"answers":["Dolphin","Lion","Lightning Bug","Albatross"],"question":"As the ship voyages past Magician Coriakins island, the voyagers in the novel The Voyage of the Dawn Treader come across an island surrounded by a shroud of utter darkness. After entering this shroud, what type of animal sheds light to help them escape?","type":"choice","answer":"Albatross"},{"answers":["Eating the fruit from the banquet table","Drinking the wine from the flagon on the table","Insulting the daughter of the Lord of the island","Touching the stone knife laying on the table"],"question":"In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, after rescuing Lord Rhoop, the voyagers land upon another island where they find a large banquet table and three Lords of Narnia, each in an enchanted sleep due to what?","type":"choice","answer":"Touching the stone knife laying on the table"},{"answers":["Foam","Ice","Frosting","Lilies"],"question":"Sailing past Ramandus island, the voyagers from The Voyage of the Dawn Treader spot a white mass on the horizon. As they approach the white mass, they discover that the sea is covered in what?","type":"choice","answer":"Lilies"},{"answers":["Caspian","Eustace","Edmund","Reepicheep"],"question":"In the novel The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, the sea eventually becomes too shallow for the ship to continue and it must turn back, but several members of the crew will continue in the landing boat, hoping to reach Aslans country. On Aslans orders, which of the following characters was made to stay with the Dawn Treader for its return voyage?","type":"choice","answer":"Caspian"},{"answers":["Sleepy","Winky","Dizzy","Dobby"],"question":"What is the name of the house-elf who warned Harry Potter of not going back to school?","type":"choice","answer":"Dobby"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Dobby, the house-elf, has been collecting Harry Potters letters to make it seem as though his friends had forgotten him.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry used the Hover Charm to destroy a pudding that Aunt Petunia had made for an important dinner party attended by Uncle Vernons potential client and the clients wife.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, the car which Harry and Ron rode on to Hogwarts, when they werent able to board on Hogwarts Express, crashed into the Whomping Willow.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Remus Lupin","Gilderoy Lockhart","Dolores Umbridge","Professor Quirrel"],"question":"What was the name of Harrys new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Gilderoy Lockhart"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Being the last to go to the barrier between platform 9 and 10 at Kings Cross Station, Harry Potter and Ron were not able to get to platform nine and three-quarters.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Parsel Language","Basilisks","Snakish","Parseltongue"],"question":"What do you call the fictional language of snakes, according to J. K. Rowlings second book in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Parseltongue"},{"answers":["She saw it lying on the floor and took it.","She found it in her trunk.","Lucius Malfoy put it in Ginnys cauldron.","She found it in the girls bathroom at Hogwarts"],"question":"How did Riddles Magical Diary go into Ginnys hand in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?","type":"choice","answer":"Lucius Malfoy put it in Ginnys cauldron."},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry Potter destroyed Riddles Diary with one of the Basilisks poisonous fangs.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Salazar Slytherin","Godric Gryffindor","Helga Hufflepuff","Rowena Ravenclaw"],"question":"Harry Potter draws a sword from the Sorting Hat during his duel with Tom Riddle and the Basilisk in the Chamber of Secrets. The sword belongs to which of the four founders of Hogwarts houses?","type":"choice","answer":"Godric Gryffindor"},{"answers":["a sock","a hat","a pair of footwear","a new shirt"],"question":"What sort of clothing freed Dobby, the house-elf, from the Malfoys according to the second Harry Potter book?","type":"choice","answer":"a sock"},{"answers":["Return of the King","Aslans Return","Return of Prince Caspian","Return to Narnia"],"question":"C.S. Lewis titled his book, Prince Caspian, after the main character, but kept one of his working titles as a subtitle. What is the subtitle of this book?","type":"choice","answer":"Return to Narnia"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"In the novel Prince Caspian, what two creatures did the dwarf Nikabrik bring into Prince Caspians counsel in an attempt to convince him to use dark magic against King Miraz?","type":"choice","answer":"A hag and a werewolf"},{"answers":["Lucy","Susan","Peter","Edmund"],"question":"Which of the Pevensie children first sees Aslan as they journey with the dwarf Trumpkin in the book Prince Caspian?","type":"choice","answer":"Lucy"},{"answers":["Miraz is betrayed and killed by his own noblemen.","Aslan stops the battle before anyone is killed.","Peter is wounded when Miraz puts his full weight into his shield.","King Miraz stumbles and falls flat on his face."],"question":"During the battle between King Miraz and Peter depicted in the book Prince Caspian, which of the following does not happen?","type":"choice","answer":"Aslan stops the battle before anyone is killed."},{"answers":["Peepicheek","Cheekipeep","Reepicheep","Mickey"],"question":"In the book Prince Caspian, what is the name of the Captain of the Mice, whom Aslan rewards with a new tail for the loyalty of his troops?","type":"choice","answer":"Reepicheep"},{"answers":["Miraz has recently had a son who he wishes to appoint as his heir.","Neither of these","Caspian is the rightful king of Narnia.","Both of these"],"question":"For what reason does King Miraz seek to kill Prince Caspian in the self-titled book?","type":"choice","answer":"Both of these"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Before leaving Narnia in the novel Prince Caspian, Aslan informs Peter and Edmund that neither of them will be returning to Narnia.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"What two creatures accompany Edmund as he delivers Peters challenge to King Miraz in the book Prince Caspian?","type":"choice","answer":"A giant and a centaur"},{"answers":["His old nurse and his tutor, Cornelius","High King Peter and King Edmund","The magician Cornelius and the lion, Aslan","His aunt, the queen and the dwarf Rikabrik"],"question":"In the novel Prince Caspian, which two people are responsible for Prince Caspians great interest in Old Narnia?","type":"choice","answer":"His old nurse and his tutor, Cornelius"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"The Tellmarines, featured in the novel Prince Caspian, are descendants of pirates that entered the land of Tellmar through a cave on an island.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Snake","Bear","Eagle","Elephant"],"question":"What is Ravenclaws symbol in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Eagle"},{"answers":["Ravenclaw","Hufflepuff","Gryffindor","Slytherin"],"question":"In which house is Susan Bones, one of the characters in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Hufflepuff"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Is Remus Lupin related to Sirius Black?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Percy","Charlie","Bill","unknown by exact text"],"question":"Who owned Scabbers before Ron Weasley?","type":"choice","answer":"Percy"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Ginny died in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the Harry Potter series, Rons uncle Billius saw a grim and died 25 hours later.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Does Harry Potter have a tattoo on his chest?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Luna","Cho","Malfoy","Anthony"],"question":"Which of these Harry Potter characters is not a member of the D.A.?","type":"choice","answer":"Malfoy"},{"answers":["Death Munchers","Death Eaters","Death Masters","Death Bugs"],"question":"What are Voldemorts followers called in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Death Eaters"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Hermiones cats name is Crookshanks.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Dark Master","Dark Lord","You-Know-Who","He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named"],"question":"Which of the following is not a name for Voldemort, the chief antagonist of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Dark Master"},{"answers":["Xewartqwe","Piilotorpho","Xenophilius","Lenopillius"],"question":"What is the name of Luna Lovegoods father in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"Xenophilius"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Professor Snape is the Potions Master in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Was Grindelwald defeated by Dumbledore in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Harry Potter marries Hermione.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Does Voldemort have a rat named Nagini?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the Disney movie, The Beauty and the Beast, all of the residents of the Beasts castle were mystical creatures.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Emma Watson plays Hermione Granger in the Harry Potter film series.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Rupert Grint","Rupert Grant","Hugh Mitchell","Richard Harris"],"question":"What English actor portrays Harry Potters best friend, Ron Weasley?","type":"choice","answer":"Rupert Grint"},{"answers":["The Fat Friar","Nearly Headless Nick","Peeves The Poltergeist","The Bloody Baron"],"question":"What Gryffindor House ghost does John Cleese play in the Harry Potter film series?","type":"choice","answer":"Nearly Headless Nick"},{"answers":["Aberforth Dumbledore","Rubeus Hagrid","Bill Weasley","Sirius Black"],"question":"What member of the Order of the Phoenix is portrayed by actor Robbie Coltrane?","type":"choice","answer":"Rubeus Hagrid"},{"answers":["Richard Martin","Robbie Coltrane","Richard Harris","Richard Griffiths"],"question":"Name the first actor who played Professor Dumbledore in the Harry Potter film series.","type":"choice","answer":"Richard Harris"},{"answers":["Tom Felton","Alan Rickman","Matthew Lewis","David Bradley"],"question":"Who portrays Draco Malfoy, one of the antagonists in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Tom Felton"},{"answers":["Emma Thompson - Sybill Trelawney","Helena Bonham Carter - Bellatrix Lestrange","Alan Rickman - Severus Snape","Jason Isaacs - Lord Voldemort"],"question":"What actor is not correctly paired with the character they played in the Harry Potter films?","type":"choice","answer":"Jason Isaacs - Lord Voldemort"},{"answers":["Everlasting Elixirs","Emerald Green Potion","Confusing Concoction","Felix Felicis"],"question":"Which potion in the Harry Potter series increases the luck of the drinker?","type":"choice","answer":"Felix Felicis"},{"answers":["Sleeping Draught","Draught of Peace","Forgetfulness Potion","Calming Draught"],"question":"This potion from the Harry Potter books induces a deep dreamless sleep in the drinker.","type":"choice","answer":"Sleeping Draught"},{"answers":["Essence of Dittany","Mandrake Restorative Draught","Skele-Gro","Amortentia"],"question":"What potion in the Harry Potter series helps stop bleeding and heal wounds?","type":"choice","answer":"Essence of Dittany"},{"answers":["Essence of Murtlap","Wolfsbane Potion","Beautification Potion","Elixir of Life"],"question":"What potion relieves the symptoms of lycanthropy in the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Wolfsbane Potion"},{"answers":["Memory Potion","Veritaserum","Babbling Beverage","Polyjuice Potion"],"question":"This potion is described by J.K. Rowling as so powerful that three drops would have you spilling your innermost secrets for the entire class to hear.","type":"choice","answer":"Veritaserum"},{"answers":["Wit-Sharpening Potion","Elixir to Induce Euphoria","Love Potion","Pepperup Potion"],"question":"In the Harry Potter books, this potion causes the drinker to become infatuated or obsessed with the one who gave it to them.","type":"choice","answer":"Love Potion"},{"answers":["Befuddlement Draught","Swelling Solution","Skele-Gro","Polyjuice Potion"],"question":"This potion, mentioned in the Harry Potter books, allows the drinker to assume the appearance of another person.","type":"choice","answer":"Polyjuice Potion"},{"answers":["Calming Draught","Shrinking Solution","Pepperup Potion","Hiccoughing Solution"],"question":"What potion is used to help treat colds in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"Pepperup Potion"},{"answers":["Strengthening Solution","Mandrake Restorative Draft","Draught of Living Death","Elixir of Life"],"question":"Which potion, introduced in Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone, lengthens the lifespan of the drinker as long as they keep drinking it?","type":"choice","answer":"Elixir of Life"},{"answers":["Aging Potion","Confusing Concoction","Swelling Solution","Befuddlement Draught"],"question":"What potion from the Harry Potter books causes the drinker to become older?","type":"choice","answer":"Aging Potion"},{"answers":["Yaxley","Bellatrix","unknown by exact text","Rookwood"],"question":"Which Death Eater killed Fred Weasley in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"unknown by exact text"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Fictional character Severus Snape was a Death Eater when he died.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Fenrir Greyback","Dolohov","Rookwood","Yaxley"],"question":"Which Death Eater bit Lupin?","type":"choice","answer":"Fenrir Greyback"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Fictional character Augustus Rookwood worked in the Department of Mysteries.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["spider","spyglass","spyer","spurr"],"question":"What is the answer to the riddle the sphinx gives to Harry Potter in the maze for the third task of of the Triwizard Tournament?","type":"choice","answer":"spider"},{"answers":["Viktor Krum","Fleur Delacour","Harry Potter","Cedric Diggory"],"question":"What is the name of the fourth champion of the fictional Triwizard Tournament?","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter"},{"answers":["The Death Eaters","Prior Incantatem","The Third Task","Flesh, Blood, and Bone"],"question":"What is the name of the chapter in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire in which Cedric Diggory dies?","type":"choice","answer":"Flesh, Blood, and Bone"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Does Harry Potter fight a dementor in the maze in the third task of the Triwizard Tournament?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Swedish Shortsnout","Chinese Fireball","Welsh Green","Hungarian Horntail"],"question":"What is the name of the dragon Viktor Krum has to fight for the first task of the Triwizard Tournament?","type":"choice","answer":"Chinese Fireball"},{"answers":["eats gillyweed","uses breathing equipment","uses bubblehead charm","transforms into a shark"],"question":"What does Harry Potter do to be able to breathe underwater for the second task of the Triwizard Tournament?","type":"choice","answer":"eats gillyweed"},{"answers":["prefects bathroom","girls bathroom","teachers bathroom","boys bathroom"],"question":"Where is Harry Potter when he finds out what the second task of the Triwizard Tournament is about?","type":"choice","answer":"prefects bathroom"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Harry Potter wins 10,000 galleons for winning the Triwizard Tournament.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["1919","1908","1925","1955"],"question":"In what year was the novel Anne of Green Gables published?","type":"choice","answer":"1908"},{"answers":["New Brunswick","Maine","Nova Scotia","Newfoundland"],"question":"What was the location of the orphanage from which Anne was adopted in the book Anne of Green Gables?","type":"choice","answer":"Nova Scotia"},{"answers":["Father and Daughter","Husband and Wife","Brother and Sister","They were cousins"],"question":"What was the relationship between Matthew and Marilla, the couple who adopted Anne in Lucy Montgomerys book?","type":"choice","answer":"Brother and Sister"},{"answers":["5","8","3","10"],"question":"How many books are there in the L. M. Montgomery Anne series?","type":"choice","answer":"8"},{"answers":["She mistook a bottle of currant wine for the raspberry cordial she was supposed to serve for tea and got drunk.","She forgot to replace the cheesecloth cover on the pudding sauce and a mouse drowned in it.","She bought hair dye from a peddler and instead of the desired black, it turned her hair green.","She broke her slate over a schoolmates head when he teasingly called her carrots."],"question":"In the book Anne of Green Gables Anne gets herself into many predicaments.  Which of the following is NOT one of them?","type":"choice","answer":"She mistook a bottle of currant wine for the raspberry cordial she was supposed to serve for tea and got drunk."},{"answers":["None of these","Prince Edward Island","New Brunswick","Nova Scotia"],"question":"In what Canadian province do Marilla and Matthew Cuthbert live in the book Anne of Green Gables?","type":"choice","answer":"Prince Edward Island"},{"answers":["Carmody","Cavendish","Avonlea","White Sands"],"question":"What is the name of the fictional town in which the story of Anne of Green Gables unfolds?","type":"choice","answer":"Avonlea"},{"answers":["Pye","Blythe","Shirley","Cuthbert"],"question":"Which of the following is Annes surname in the book Anne of Green Gables?","type":"choice","answer":"Shirley"},{"answers":["Two peas in a pod","Bosom friends","Truer than blue","Friends til the end"],"question":"Diana Barry is Annes best friend in the book Anne of Green Gables. How did Anne describe their friendship?","type":"choice","answer":"Bosom friends"},{"answers":["1960","1964","1970","1972"],"question":"When was Anne of Green Gables - The Musical performed for the first time?","type":"choice","answer":"1964"},{"answers":["They dont have flounces.","They dont have petticoats.","They dont have puffed sleeves.","They dont have any lace trimming."],"question":"Early in the story of Anne of Green Gables, Marilla proudly presents Anne with three new dresses which she has made to replace the shabby, orphanage issued clothes but is very annoyed when it becomes obvious that Anne doesnt like them. Why doesnt Anne like them?","type":"choice","answer":"They dont have puffed sleeves."},{"answers":["The Green Gables Theater of the Arts","The Cradle of Confederation Theater","The Centennial Theater of the Arts","The Confederation Center of the Arts"],"question":"What is the name of the theater in which Anne of Green Gables - The Musical plays every summer?","type":"choice","answer":"The Confederation Center of the Arts"},{"answers":["Colleen Dewhurst","Ellen Burstyn","Patricia Hamilton","Rosemary Radcliff"],"question":"This Emmy Award-winning actress played Marilla in the 1985 television production of Anne of Green Gables, written and directed by Kevin Sullivan.","type":"choice","answer":"Colleen Dewhurst"},{"answers":["All of these","Bossy","Prying","Opinionated"],"question":"What adjective best describes the character of Mrs. Rachel Lynde from the book Anne of Green Gables?","type":"choice","answer":"All of these"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"At the end of the novel Anne of Green Gables, Matthew Cuthbert dies from complications related to pneumonia.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["$2.50","$250.00","$25.00","$25.50"],"question":"Sam had $3.00, Bob had $9.50, Joe had $5.25, and Jim had $7.25. How much is all of their money together worth?","type":"choice","answer":"$25.00"},{"answers":["11","9","12","6"],"question":"Which one of these numbers does not fit in the sequence: 2 4 6 7 9 12 11?","type":"choice","answer":"12"},{"answers":["32.1","3.21","1.23","12.3"],"question":"What do you get when you divide 123 by 10?","type":"choice","answer":"12.3"},{"answers":["284","824","428","842"],"question":"There are three digits in this number. The first digit (of the hundreds) is 8. Divide it by two, that is your second digit, divide the result again by two, that is your third digit. What is the number?","type":"choice","answer":"842"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Do all of these numbers fit the sequence: 1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 9?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["74.5","76.5","76","75"],"question":"How much is 765 divided by 10?","type":"choice","answer":"76.5"},{"answers":["3","9","15","20"],"question":"Which of the following numbers doesnt belong to the others: 3, 9, 15, 20?","type":"choice","answer":"20"},{"answers":["16","32","8","4"],"question":"A person owned 8 dogs and as many cats. What is the total amount of pets owned by that somebody?","type":"choice","answer":"16"},{"answers":["Hufflepuffs cup","The locket","None of these","Nagini"],"question":"What is the first Horcrux found in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"The locket"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Did Harry Potter destroy Tom Riddles diary in the second book because he knew it was a Horcrux?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Gryffindors sword","Their Wands","Nothing, Harry destroyed it.","Basilisk Fangs"],"question":"What did Ron and Hermione use to destroy Hufflepuffs cup?","type":"choice","answer":"Basilisk Fangs"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"One of the Horcruxes in the Harry Potter books is Ravenclaws cup.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["10","7","2","5"],"question":"How many Horcruxes did Tom Riddle make?","type":"choice","answer":"7"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"According to the Harry Potter series of books, any object can be a Horcrux.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"If one of Voldemorts Horcruxes is destroyed, will he know?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Nagini, one of Voldemorts Horcruxes, is a snake.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["13","55","22","7"],"question":"How old was Charlotte, the protagonist of The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, when she took the trip from England to her home on Rhode Island?","type":"choice","answer":"13"},{"answers":["The Seahawk","The Seacraft","The Doyle Express","The Charlotte Doyle"],"question":"What was the name of the ship that Charlotte boarded in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle?","type":"choice","answer":"The Seahawk"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, the crew wanted to get revenge on the Captain.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Charlotte was the only female on the ship in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, the men from the crew plan to kill Charlotte because she supported the Captain.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Zachariah, a character from the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, is brutally beaten to death by the Captain and Mr. Hollybrass.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Charlotte","The ships ghost","Himself","Zachariah"],"question":"Who does the Captain blame for the murder of Mr. Hollybrass in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle?","type":"choice","answer":"Charlotte"},{"answers":["hanging","a week in the brig","getting your hands cut off","getting locked in a room with the ships ghost"],"question":"According to the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, what is the penalty for murder of a ships First Mate?","type":"choice","answer":"hanging"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The Captain in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle dies.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Her soul","Her heart","Her tongue/voice","Her necklace"],"question":"What does the Sea Witch want from the Little Mermaid in exchange for the magic potion in Andersens fairy tale The Little Mermaid?","type":"choice","answer":"Her tongue/voice"},{"answers":["Someone is dying","God is crying","Someone is born","An angel is coming to earth from Heaven"],"question":"What is the meaning of a falling star according to the late grandmother in Andersens The Little Match Girl?","type":"choice","answer":"Someone is dying"},{"answers":["They put it in the Royal Museum","They split it and eat it","An anger takes it to Heaven",""],"question":"What happens to the pea after the prince marries the princess in the fairy tale The Princess and the Pea?","type":"choice","answer":"They put it in the Royal Museum"},{"answers":["Smile","Cut her hair","Go out in the sunlight","Speak"],"question":"What is Elisa forbidden to do until she finishes knitting the eleven nettle shirts in Hans Christian Andersens fairy tale The Wild Swans?","type":"choice","answer":"Speak"},{"answers":["Forgiveness","Eternity","Love","Purity"],"question":"What is the word that Kai has to spell using pieces of ice in order to regain his freedom in Andersens fairy tale The Snow Queen?","type":"choice","answer":"Eternity"},{"answers":["Bella","Rosalind","Maya","Lily"],"question":"What new name is Thumbelina given at the end of the fairy tale Thumbelina?","type":"choice","answer":"Maya"},{"answers":["Cat and dog","Cat and hen","Hen and dog","Geese"],"question":"What animals mock the little duck in Hans Christian Andersens fairy tale The Ugly Duckling?","type":"choice","answer":"Cat and hen"},{"answers":["Liars","Stupid people","Criminals","All of these"],"question":"What kind of people are unable to see the clothes of the emperor according to the frauds in the fairy tale The Emperors New Clothes?","type":"choice","answer":"Stupid people"},{"answers":["They are dressed in white","They are both standing on one leg","They love listening to the gramophone","They are both very sad"],"question":"According to The Steadfast Tin Soldier, what do the tin soldier and the paper ballerina have in common that makes the soldier fall in love?","type":"choice","answer":"They are both standing on one leg"},{"answers":["God forces him to go away","He is moved by the song of the bird","He takes the Emperors nightingale in exchange for his life","He gets scared from a Chinese mask"],"question":"Why does Death decide to spare the Chinese Emperors life in the fairy tale The Nightingale by Hans Christian Andersen?","type":"choice","answer":"He is moved by the song of the bird"},{"answers":["54","50","52","53"],"question":"How many people died in the fictional Battle of Hogwarts?","type":"choice","answer":"54"},{"answers":["25","26","29","28"],"question":"How many people are in the fictional student organisation known as Dumbledores Army?","type":"choice","answer":"28"},{"answers":["3","5","4","6"],"question":"How many siblings does Ron Weasley have?","type":"choice","answer":"6"},{"answers":["5","1","4","3"],"question":"How many people were selected for the Triwizard Tournament in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?","type":"choice","answer":"4"},{"answers":["15","9","10","8"],"question":"How many O.W.L.s did Hermione Granger get in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"10"},{"answers":["55","45","40","50"],"question":"How many dementors attacked Harry and Hermione in the end of Book 3 of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"50"},{"answers":["9","8","6","7"],"question":"How many floors are in the fictional Hogwarts school?(excluding the dungeons)","type":"choice","answer":"7"},{"answers":["December 25th","November 25th","October 25th","January 25th"],"question":"On what day did Harry Potter discover the Mirror of Erised?","type":"choice","answer":"December 25th"},{"answers":["5th","7th","6th","3rd"],"question":"On what floor of the fictional Hogwarts school do you find the Room of Requirement?","type":"choice","answer":"7th"},{"answers":["2","3","4","1"],"question":"How many people died in the book Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone?","type":"choice","answer":"3"},{"answers":["Whats this doing here?","Ouch!","Hush up Hedwig","What the?"],"question":"What is Harrys first line in the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"What the?"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Fictional character Rita Skeeter wrote a book titled Albus Dumbledore, His Life and Lies.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Was Albus Dumbledores sister named Areida?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Fred Weasley","Arthur Weasley","Kingsley Shacklebolt","Bill Weasley"],"question":"Who does Hermione Granger fly with when leaving Privet Drive?","type":"choice","answer":"Kingsley Shacklebolt"},{"answers":["Suctesemptra","Muffliato","Demuestio","Fiendfyre"],"question":"What spell does Hermione not approve of according to the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"Muffliato"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Ron leaves the group when they are in the forest of Dean.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Ron","Harry","Hermione","Ginny"],"question":"What character first discovered that the name Voldemort was cursed?","type":"choice","answer":"Ron"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"It is mentioned in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows that Bill had a real knack for guessing the passwords for the radio.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Dragomir","He doesnt use unforgivable curses.","","Travers"],"question":"Who does Harry first use the Imperius curse on in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"A goblin"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"According to the Harry Potter books, Fleur Delacours middle name is Clemence.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Gemino","Duplique","Multiplico","Magrante"],"question":"What is the name of the spell that multiplies objects in the Harry Potter books?","type":"choice","answer":"Gemino"},{"answers":["Mulciber and Avery","Macnair and Lucius","James and Sirius","Lucius and Lestrange"],"question":"In the chapter of Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows, titled The Princes Tale, Lily states that these two boys idea of humor is, just evil.","type":"choice","answer":"Mulciber and Avery"},{"answers":["Hermione","McGonagall","Ginny","Ron"],"question":"What characters screams at the end of Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows on learning of Harrys apparent death.","type":"choice","answer":"McGonagall"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Does Voldemort tell Neville that he has spirit and bravery in the last book of the Harry Potter series?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["May 25, 1944","January 29, 1959","August 1, 1966","February 14, 1951"],"question":"Sleeping Beauty was the last fairy tale produced by Walt Disney.  When was it released?","type":"choice","answer":"January 29, 1959"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Sleeping Beautys musical score and songs were inspired by Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovskys Sleeping Beauty ballet.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["The goddess of the dawn","The goddess of the moon","The goddess of the forests","The goddess of the clouds"],"question":"In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, Princess Aurora is born to King Stefan and Queen Leah and they name her Aurora after what Roman goddess?","type":"choice","answer":"The goddess of the dawn"},{"answers":["She was in line to inherit the kingdom before Aurora was born.","She is in love with the king.","She hates the queen, her sister.","She was not invited to the christening."],"question":"In the popular Disney animated film Maleficent curses baby Aurora: she will die when she pricks her finger on a spinning wheels spindle.  Why does Maleficent arrive and curse the child?","type":"choice","answer":"She was not invited to the christening."},{"answers":["She makes Aurora able to live for 500 years.","She weakens the curse so Aurora will only fall into a deep sleep.","She curses Maleficent with death.","She makes a valiant prince fall in love with Aurora."],"question":"What is the gift of the third fairy in the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty?","type":"choice","answer":"She weakens the curse so Aurora will only fall into a deep sleep."},{"answers":["locks Aurora in a tower","tries to have another witch remove the curse","commands all spinning wheels be destroyed","kills Maleficent"],"question":"The three fairies in the animated film Sleeping Beauty decide to conceal Aurora in a cabin in the woods until her 16th birthday passes, but before the fairies take Aurora to the woods, what does the King do to stop the curse?","type":"choice","answer":"commands all spinning wheels be destroyed"},{"answers":["Dahlia","Topaz","Briar Rose","Jasmine"],"question":"What do the fairies rename Aurora in the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty?","type":"choice","answer":"Briar Rose"},{"answers":["She consults her crystal ball for Aurora.","She sends out her raven Diablo to find Aurora.","She disguises herself as a peasant and searches for Aurora.","She puts the prince under a spell and sends him to search for Aurora."],"question":"In the animated movie Sleeping Beauty, just prior to Auroras 16th birthday, Maleficent is furious that she and her evil henchmen still cannot find Aurora. What does Maleficent do?","type":"choice","answer":"She sends out her raven Diablo to find Aurora."},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"In the movie Sleeping Beauty, on Auroras 16th birthday, the fairies decide to make two presents, but their attempts fail and they use their wands, thus giving away their location. What two items were the fairies making for Aurora?","type":"choice","answer":"A cake and a gown"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, when Aurora returns to the cabin, the fairies tell her who she really is and take her to the castle to see her parents.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["The queen","The king","The fairies","The prince"],"question":"In the movie Sleeping Beauty, back at home in the castle, Aurora finds a spinning wheel in the castles tower, pricks her finger on the spindle and falls into a deep sleep. Who finds Aurora?","type":"choice","answer":"The fairies"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, once Aurora falls into her deep sleep, the fairies freeze time until the spell is broken.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["The Lair","The Den of Thorns","The Forbidden Mountain","The Dark Palace"],"question":"In the Disney film Sleeping Beauty, the fairies find out that Prince Phillip is the man Aurora loves and the only one who can break the spell, but Maleficents henchmen capture him and take him to Maleficents castle. What is the castle called?","type":"choice","answer":"The Forbidden Mountain"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"In the animated movie Sleeping Beauty, the fairies enter Maleficents castle and free the prince and give him these two magical objects.","type":"choice","answer":"A sword and a shield"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"After Maleficent dies in the film Sleeping Beauty, Prince Phillip rushes to Aurora and removes the curse with a kiss. The two enter the palaces ballroom and see Auroras parents. Is this the first time Aurora has seen her parents since she was an infant?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Pink","Blue","Purple","Green"],"question":"In the animated film Sleeping Beauty, Aurora and Prince Phillip dance a waltz and do not notice the fairies magically changing the color of Auroras ball gown.  As the book closes, Auroras gown turns this color and remains this color.","type":"choice","answer":"Pink"},{"answers":["$102.49 million","$478.22 million","$668.39 million","$309.2 million"],"question":"Sleeping Beauty was re-released theatrically in 1970, 1971, 1986, 1993, 1995, and 2008. How much did it gross in theatres in the period 1959-2009, when adjusted for ticket price inflation?","type":"choice","answer":"$478.22 million"},{"answers":["She joked that she stayed because she was in love with Rupert Grint.","Her parents talked her into staying.","She did it for the fans.","She couldnt bear to see anyone else play Hermione."],"question":"Why did actress Emma Watson, who plays Hermione in the Harry Potter series, keep her role in the sixth movie, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009, after initially deciding to quit?","type":"choice","answer":"She couldnt bear to see anyone else play Hermione."},{"answers":["Comic character","Unique character","Tragic character","Ambiguous character"],"question":"How did actor Jim Broadbent describe his character, Horace Slughorn, from the sixth Harry Potter movie, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009?","type":"choice","answer":"Comic character"},{"answers":["Kate Winslet","Meg Ryan","Naomi Watts","Melanie Griffith"],"question":"This actress reportedly accepted the role of Narcissa Malfoy for the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, but her agent stated that the rumors were not true.","type":"choice","answer":"Naomi Watts"},{"answers":["Draco Malfoy","Albus Dumbledore","Severus Snape","Sirius Black"],"question":"Who turns out to be the Half-Blood Prince in the sixth Harry Potter movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Severus Snape"},{"answers":["Bagger","Padfoot","Mole","Dazzler"],"question":"What is the nickname of Sirius Black, whose younger brother Regulus Black appears in a photograph owned by Horace Slughorn in the movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009?","type":"choice","answer":"Padfoot"},{"answers":["Fleur Delacour","Lavender Brown","All of these","Ginny Weasley"],"question":"With whom does Harry Potter form a relationship in the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Ginny Weasley"},{"answers":["Dumbledores funeral was not in the script.","Both the battle in the castle and Dumbledores funeral were not in the script.","The climactic battle in the castle was not in the script.","No changes were made."],"question":"What are the differences between the original plot of the book and the script of 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Both the battle in the castle and Dumbledores funeral were not in the script."},{"answers":["David Copperfield","Peter Pan","Adolf Hitler","Harry Potter"],"question":"What popular personality did actor Daniel Radcliffe portray in his debut movie?","type":"choice","answer":"David Copperfield"},{"answers":["One of Noahs sons","","Noah",""],"question":"What kind of character did actor Rupert Grint from the 2009 Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince depict in a play based on the story of Noahs Ark when he was little?","type":"choice","answer":"A fish"},{"answers":["Helena Bonham Carter","Jessie Cave","Bonnie Wright","Emma Watson"],"question":"Which of these cast members of the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince was born in Paris, France?","type":"choice","answer":"Emma Watson"},{"answers":["Nightingale","Sparrow","Hummingbird","Swallow"],"question":"What kind of bird is the character from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Happy Prince?","type":"choice","answer":"Swallow"},{"answers":["It steals one","It paints a white rose with its blood","It travels trough many countries and dies from exhaustion","It prays to God and He sends one"],"question":"How does the nightingale from Oscar Wildes story The Nightingale and the Rose find a red rose for the poor student?","type":"choice","answer":"It paints a white rose with its blood"},{"answers":["There is no more sunshine in the garden, only darkness","The small pond dries up and the fish dies","All the flowers wither and the birds die","Eternal winter sets in the garden"],"question":"What happens to the beautiful garden of the giant when he builds a wall to keep children off in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Selfish Giant?","type":"choice","answer":"Eternal winter sets in the garden"},{"answers":["He is a musician","He is a miller","Hes a gardener","Hes a doctor"],"question":"What does Hans from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Devoted Friend do for a living?","type":"choice","answer":"Hes a gardener"},{"answers":["It is too lofty","It dies","It is faulty","It gets wet"],"question":"Why does the rocket from Oscar Wildes story The Remarkable Rocket fail to ignite?","type":"choice","answer":"It gets wet"},{"answers":["He doesnt want to be a king","He has nightmares of where it came from","All of these","He finds it ugly"],"question":"Why does the shepherd from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Young King refuse to wear the royal raiment?","type":"choice","answer":"He has nightmares of where it came from"},{"answers":["Its a shame Ive forgotten who I was, so let the people decide my fate.","For the future, let those who come to play with me have no hearts.","Little people will never know what its like being a princess.","Justice shall reign one day when I sit on the throne."],"question":"What is the last line of the Infanta from Oscar Wildes story The Birthday of the Infanta?","type":"choice","answer":"For the future, let those who come to play with me have no hearts."},{"answers":["His only child","His hope","His most valuable possession","His heart"],"question":"What does the Soul want from the fisherman in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Fisherman and his Soul?","type":"choice","answer":"His heart"},{"answers":["","An angel","",""],"question":"Who is the mother of the Star-Child from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Star-Child?","type":"choice","answer":"A beggar"},{"answers":["","","Vapor",""],"question":"What is the beautiful Star-Child transformed into in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Star-Child?","type":"choice","answer":"A cross between a snake and a toad"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Harry Potter, Voldemort, and Dumbledore have connected wands.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Voldemort","Rookwood","Bellatrix","Igor Karkaroff"],"question":"Which of these fictional characters is the leader of the Death Eaters?","type":"choice","answer":"Voldemort"},{"answers":["Michael","John","Robert","James"],"question":"What was the first name of the animated 1980s hero Blackstar?","type":"choice","answer":"John"},{"answers":["After an impact with an asteroid","Because of his co-pilots incompetence","After a time rift","After falling in a black hole"],"question":"How did Blackstar from the animated series of the same name get stranded in the alien world?","type":"choice","answer":"After falling in a black hole"},{"answers":["1980","1981","1983","1979"],"question":"In what year were the Blackstar animated series first broadcast on American television?","type":"choice","answer":"1981"},{"answers":["Burble","Carpo","Dargo","Balkar"],"question":"In the Blackstar animates series, which of these was not a name of the little people known as the Trobbits?","type":"choice","answer":"Dargo"},{"answers":["16","13","20","10"],"question":"How many episodes of the animated series Blackstar ran on American television?","type":"choice","answer":"13"},{"answers":["William Horwood","E. H. Shepard","Kenneth Grahame","A. A. Milne"],"question":"The Wind in the Willows was published in 1908 without much notice. What famous author and playwright, best known for Winnie the Pooh, adapted part of the book for the stage in 1929, thus making the book famous?","type":"choice","answer":"A. A. Milne"},{"answers":["trying to sleep","listening to Mr. Toad","spring cleaning","looking for food"],"question":"At the beginning of the book The Wind in the Willows, what is Mole doing when he gets angry and goes above ground to the river?","type":"choice","answer":"spring cleaning"},{"answers":["Mole","Mr. Toad","Weasel","Pan"],"question":"What character from The Wind in the Willows becomes easily obsessed with items, only to forget about them soon after acquiring them?","type":"choice","answer":"Mr. Toad"},{"answers":["E. H. Shepard","A. A. Milne","Kenneth Grahame","James Blish"],"question":"The Wind in the Willows was first published in 1908. What Scottish-born writer and author of the story The Reluctant Dragon wrote this book?","type":"choice","answer":"Kenneth Grahame"},{"answers":["Otter","Mr. Toad","Mole","Weasel"],"question":"What character from The Wind in the Willows gets lost in Wild Wood while looking for Badgers house?","type":"choice","answer":"Mole"},{"answers":["Put him under house arrest","Have him thrown in jail","Burn his cars","Make him live underground with Mole"],"question":"In the novel The Wind in the Willows, Toad has crashed 6 cars, been put in the hospital for injuries 3 times, and has spent a great deal of money on fines. Toads friends decide to do this to save Toad since he has no sense when it comes to his obsessions.","type":"choice","answer":"Put him under house arrest"},{"answers":["Toads cellmate","The jailer","Toads attorney","The jailers daughter"],"question":"In the novel The Wind in the Willows, while Mr. Toad is in jail, this person becomes fond of him and helps him escape.","type":"choice","answer":"The jailers daughter"},{"answers":["","An attractive female","The jailer",""],"question":"In order to escape, Toad from The Wind in the Willows is dressed in disguise. What is he disguised as?","type":"choice","answer":"A washerwoman"},{"answers":["Money and stew","","Another disguise",""],"question":"In the book The Wind in the Willows, shortly after his escape and still in disguise, Mr. Toad meets a bargewoman and tricks her into giving him a job. The bargewoman discovers Toads trick and throws him overboard. He steals her horse and sells it to a Gypsy for what?","type":"choice","answer":"Money and stew"},{"answers":["It is Toads car, and Badger is the driver","It is Rats car, and Badger is the driver","It is the same car that Toad stole earlier","It is an undercover police car"],"question":"In The Wind in the Willows, Mr. Toad tries to hitchhike back to the River Bank community. What is the significance of the car and driver that give Toad a ride?","type":"choice","answer":"It is the same car that Toad stole earlier"},{"answers":["the weasels, stoats and ferrets","the rabbits and otters","the birds","the squirrels and chipmunks"],"question":"After his jail escape, The Wind in the Willows character, Toad, learns from Ratty that Toad Hall has been taken over by these Wild Wood animals.","type":"choice","answer":"the weasels, stoats and ferrets"},{"answers":["Chicken Little","Rip Van Winkle","The Legend of Sleepy Hollow","Mickey and the Beanstalk"],"question":"In 1949 Disney released their animated versions of The Wind in the Willows and this short story.","type":"choice","answer":"The Legend of Sleepy Hollow"},{"answers":["The Doors","Jethro Tull","The Beatles","Pink Floyd"],"question":"In 1967 this British rock band released their first album. It was titled after Chapter 7 of The Wind in the Willows: The Piper at the Gates of Dawn.","type":"choice","answer":"Pink Floyd"},{"answers":["a ride at Disneyland","a brand of tennis shoes","a Wyoming state police manual","a board game"],"question":"Based on Mr. Toads car driving in The Wind in the Willows, Mr. Toads Wild Ride was established in 1955. What is it?","type":"choice","answer":"a ride at Disneyland"},{"answers":["Fairy Hollow","London","Never Land","Mollusk Island"],"question":"Where does Peter live in the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves?","type":"choice","answer":"Mollusk Island"},{"answers":["Raven","Dana","Brilliant Ruby","Shining Pearl"],"question":"In Peter and the Shadow Thieves, what is the name of Fighting Prawns oldest daughter?","type":"choice","answer":"Shining Pearl"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Does Peter, the main character in Peter and the Shadow Thieves, wear shoes?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["Singer","Beauty","Teacher","Swimmer"],"question":"What is the name of the mermaid that flirts with Peter in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?","type":"choice","answer":"Teacher"},{"answers":["Louise","Tina","Molly","Julie"],"question":"Who does Peter have to warn about Ombra in the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves?","type":"choice","answer":"Molly"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves, Slank is one of the Aster guards.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["He takes a taxi.","He goes by boat.","He flies.","He swims."],"question":"How does Peter get to London in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?","type":"choice","answer":"He goes by boat."},{"answers":["Bloody Tower","White Tower","Prison Tower","Golden Tower"],"question":"In the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves, the starstuff was in what tower?","type":"choice","answer":"White Tower"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves, James and Thomas are the two fastest Lost boys.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Rosy Tone","Hornblower","Tinker Bell","Violet Vinger"],"question":"Which fairy is Peters guardian in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?","type":"choice","answer":"Tinker Bell"},{"answers":["Decoy Detonator","Pygmy Puff","Fever Fudge","Nose Bleed Nougat"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, when Harry is visiting Weasleys Wizard Wheezes, what is the last product mentioned before he followed Draco Malfoy into Knockturn Alley?","type":"choice","answer":"Pygmy Puff"},{"answers":["Beech","Whomping Willow","Spruce","Oak"],"question":"What kind of tree does Harry Potter sit under after Dumbledores funeral?","type":"choice","answer":"Beech"},{"answers":["Water","Dittany","Draught of Living Death","Toadspawn"],"question":"The first time Harry Potter encounters a little girl outside the room of requirement, she drops a bottle of what?","type":"choice","answer":"Toadspawn"},{"answers":["Pine","Walnut","Oak","Chestnut"],"question":"What is Bellatrix Lestranges wand made of?","type":"choice","answer":"Walnut"},{"answers":["Brocks","Books","Brooks","Brakes"],"question":"What is Zoeys last name on the TV show Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"Brooks"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"On the sitcom Zoey 101, Zoeys brothers name is Todd.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Did Lola pretend to be a freaky goth chick on the show Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Has Chase had a crush on Zoey on the sitcom Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["2006","2004","2005","2003"],"question":"What year did the TV series Zoey 101 hit the airwaves?","type":"choice","answer":"2005"},{"answers":["Mrs Rivers","Dean Matthews","Ms. Matthews","Dean Rivers"],"question":"Who is the principal of the high school on Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"Dean Rivers"},{"answers":["ACP","PAC","PCA","CAP"],"question":"What is the name of Zoeys high school on Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"PCA"},{"answers":["Quinn","Nicole","Ginger","Gretchen"],"question":"What is the name of Zoeys brainiac friend on the sitcom Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"Quinn"},{"answers":["She went to an all girls school.","She got expelled.","She moved away.","She went to home school."],"question":"What happened to Nicole on the TV show Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"She went to an all girls school."},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Logan Ryan is the spoiled rich boy on Zoey 101.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Sally","Sam","Stacey","Sidney"],"question":"What  Zoey 101 character has a lisp?","type":"choice","answer":"Stacey"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Did Zoey start dating James when Chase went to England.","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Has Quinn dated Marc on the show Zoey 101?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["2009","2007","2006","2008"],"question":"When did Zoey 101 end its original run?","type":"choice","answer":"2008"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Jamie Lynn Spears plays Zoey on Zoey 101.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["No","Yes"],"question":"Is there a host for the Arcade on Webkinz?","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["cow","panda","bear","monkey"],"question":"What type of animal is the school superintendent on Webkinz?","type":"choice","answer":"cow"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"On Webkinz, there is a host for the Tournament Area.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["2","5","15","10"],"question":"How many tokens do you need to access the Wish Machine in Webkinz World?","type":"choice","answer":"10"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"Dr. Quacks Clinic is the doctors office in Webkinz world.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["100","10","1","50"],"question":"In Webkinz World, What is the maximum amount of Kinzcash (from the tips can) that Arte will accept?","type":"choice","answer":"100"},{"answers":["Ginny","Both","Harry","Said"],"question":"What is the 150th to last word in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?","type":"choice","answer":"Both"},{"answers":["They","Aberforth","Came","Hallows"],"question":"In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, there is a chapter called The Bribe. What is the 138th word in this chapter?","type":"choice","answer":"They"},{"answers":["It","The","By","Hermione"],"question":"This word is the 367th word of Hermiones Secret in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.","type":"choice","answer":"By"},{"answers":["Sirius","Grim","Send","Letter"],"question":"What is the 120th word in Grim Defeat, a chapter of Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.","type":"choice","answer":"Send"},{"answers":["Happy","Hedwig","Great","Hagrid"],"question":"What is the 105th to last word in Diagon Alley, a chapter in Harry Potter and the Sorcerers/Philosophers Stone?","type":"choice","answer":"Great"},{"answers":["Snake","Filch","Malfoy","Everyone"],"question":"This word is the 224th word of the chapter, titled The Midnight Duel in Harry Potter and the Sorcerers/Philosophers Stone.","type":"choice","answer":"Everyone"},{"answers":["Riddle","Rocks","Lockhart","Serpents"],"question":"Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets has a chapter called The Chamber of Secrets. What is the 83rd to last word in this chapter?","type":"choice","answer":"Serpents"},{"answers":["Wand","Malfoy","Ron","Tongue"],"question":"In the Dueling Club, a chapter in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, what is the 251st to last word?","type":"choice","answer":"Tongue"},{"answers":["Anyone","Throat","Elf","Harry"],"question":"This is word number 230 in the chapter Elf Tails in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.","type":"choice","answer":"Throat"},{"answers":[null,"Wishing they never left","Sooner then you think","Waiting for their mommy","Wagging their tails behind them"],"question":"Whats the last line of the nursery rhyme Little Bo Peep:","type":"choice","answer":"Wagging their tails behind them"},{"answers":["","","",""],"question":"Fill in the missing words in the nursery rhyme Hush, Little Baby:","type":"choice","answer":"A diamond ring"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the following division problem, the quotient is 2: ","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Scratching him/herself","Trying to get attention","Playing around","Taking a bath"],"question":"If your dog is licking him/herself, he/she is actually doing this.","type":"choice","answer":"Taking a bath"},{"answers":["Play in","Sleep in","Use the bathroom in","Eat in"],"question":"Kittens use the litter box as a place to what?","type":"choice","answer":"Use the bathroom in"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"When dogs lick you, to them it is the same as kissing you.","type":"choice","answer":"No"},{"answers":["modifies clauses","modifies nouns","modifies adjectives","modifies verbs"],"question":"Which of the following is NOT true about an adverb?","type":"choice","answer":"modifies nouns"},{"answers":["her","along","walking","Jane"],"question":"What is the participle in the following sentence?  Jane noticed her father walking along the shoreline.","type":"choice","answer":"walking"},{"answers":["door","mom","lazy","car"],"question":"Which of the following words can be used as an adjective?","type":"choice","answer":"lazy"},{"answers":["Josh could only go one-way.","The cherries were chocolate-covered.","Edgar Allen Poe is well-known.","Josh was driving down a one-way street."],"question":"Two words can be brought together as a compound word.  They can be written together (one way), written as one word (hairstylist) or written with a hyphen (forty-two).  Which of the following sentences is a correct usage of a hyphen?","type":"choice","answer":"Josh was driving down a one-way street."},{"answers":["noun","adjective","adverb","verb"],"question":"The word effect is used as what part of speech in the following sentence?  Will lack of sleep have an effect on your performance at work?","type":"choice","answer":"noun"},{"answers":["To stay in shape for competition, athletes must exercise on a regular basis to ensure top performance.","Most of the evidence seemed convincing. Still, the credibility of some witnesses was in question.","Preparing and submitting his report to the review board for evaluation and possible publication, was one of the most difficult tasks Bill had ever attempted.","After the adjustment for inflation, real wages have decreased while corporate profits have grown."],"question":"Which of the following sentences uses a comma incorrectly?","type":"choice","answer":"Preparing and submitting his report to the review board for evaluation and possible publication, was one of the most difficult tasks Bill had ever attempted."},{"answers":["Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets","Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire","Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone","Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"],"question":"In which movie did Hermione Granger say the following:","type":"choice","answer":"Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone"},{"answers":["Bam-Bam","Jean-Claude Van Damme","Sam",""],"question":"Complete this line from the classic childrens book Green Eggs and Ham:","type":"choice","answer":"Sam"},{"answers":["Clock","Dog with Chicken Pox","Bag of Rocks","Fox"],"question":"Complete this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:","type":"choice","answer":"Fox"},{"answers":["Jeep","Car","Line at the DMV","Bucket of boiled beets"],"question":"What word is missing in this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:","type":"choice","answer":"Car"},{"answers":["The Black Cauldron","Sleeping Beauty","Lady and the Tramp","Beauty and the Beast"],"question":"In what Disney film does the following exchange take place:","type":"choice","answer":"Beauty and the Beast"},{"answers":[null,null,"The Emperors New Groove","The Brave Little Toaster","Mulan",""],"question":"What Disney film is this dialogue from:","type":"choice","answer":"The Emperors New Groove"},{"answers":["4","2","8","6"],"question":"What does x equal in this equation?","type":"choice","answer":"2"},{"answers":["0","5","10","2"],"question":"What is the answer to the following:","type":"choice","answer":"5"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Is this correct?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["16","17","14","15"],"question":"What is the missing number?","type":"choice","answer":"16"},{"answers":["2001","2000","2002","2003"],"question":"What year did the animated series The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius 1st air?","type":"choice","answer":"2002"},{"answers":["Carl and Bolbi","Carl and Sheen","Bolbi and Nick","Sheen and Bob"],"question":"Who  are Jimmys best friends on the show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?","type":"choice","answer":"Carl and Sheen"},{"answers":["Johnson and Vortex","Folfax and Vortex","Weed and Anderson","Williams and Washington"],"question":"What are Libbys and Cindys last names on the animated show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?","type":"choice","answer":"Folfax and Vortex"},{"answers":["Super  Justice League","The Tomorrow Boys","The N-Men","Fundemonium"],"question":"In what episode of The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius are Jimmy and friends diagnosed with superpowers?","type":"choice","answer":"The N-Men"},{"answers":["Bat Man","UltraLord","Speed Boy","Super Man"],"question":"On the animated show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius, who is Sheens favorite  superhero?","type":"choice","answer":"UltraLord"},{"answers":["Oak Town","Retro Park","Retroland","Retroville"],"question":"What city do Jimmy and his friends live in on the show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?","type":"choice","answer":"Retroville"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"In the series The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius, Jimmy has a crush on Cindy.","type":"choice","answer":"True"},{"answers":["Robert","James","Joseph","Hugh"],"question":"What is Jimmys dads name on The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?","type":"choice","answer":"Hugh"},{"answers":["pie","cookies","pizza","cake"],"question":"What is Jimmys dads favorite food on The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?","type":"choice","answer":"pie"},{"answers":["Ms. Fowl","Mrs. Poultry","Ms. Turkey","Ms. Chicken"],"question":"Who is the teacher of fictional character Jimmy Neutron?","type":"choice","answer":"Ms. Fowl"},{"answers":["Yes","No"],"question":"Does animated character Jimmy Neutron have a  brother?","type":"choice","answer":"Yes"},{"answers":["Fear of monsters under your bed","Fear of lemon meringue pie","Fear of heights","Fear of realtors"],"question":"Which of these is a rational fear according to the book the The Wide Window by Lemony Snicket?","type":"choice","answer":"Fear of monsters under your bed"},{"answers":["True","False"],"question":"In the book The Austere Academy, when Carmelita Spats called the Baudelaires cakesniffers, Mr. Poe said that was very rude of her.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["The Penultimate Peril","The Wide Window","The Vile Village","The Bad Beginning"],"question":"In which book by Lemony Snicket does the phrase, It takes a village to raise a child, affect the Baudelaires?","type":"choice","answer":"The Vile Village"},{"answers":["They are just rectangles of black.","They look like someone spilled tea on them.","They can only be read if you hold the book up to a mirror.","They are deliberately placed out of order."],"question":"Which statement is true about some of the pages of the book The Ersatz Elevator?","type":"choice","answer":"They are just rectangles of black."},{"answers":["The Carnivorous Carnival","The Reptile Room","The Grim Grotto","The Vile Village"],"question":"In which book of A Series of Unfortunate Events are there two pages that are almost identical?","type":"choice","answer":"The Carnivorous Carnival"},{"answers":["To Beatrice, when I first saw you, I was breathless. Now, you are.","To Beatrice, summer without you is as cold as winter. Winter without you is even colder.","To Beatrice, I always used to sleep late on weekends. Alas, now you do, also.","To Beatrice, you will always be in my mind, in my heart, and in your grave."],"question":"Every book of A Series of Unfortunate Events is dedicated to Beatrice, followed by a short message. Which of the following sentences was never written on the dedication page?","type":"choice","answer":"To Beatrice, I always used to sleep late on weekends. Alas, now you do, also."},{"answers":["Ratennice","Centarine","Nectarine","Nernatice"],"question":"Decode the name of this fruit:","type":"choice","answer":"Nectarine"},{"answers":["","Beatrice Quagmire","Beatrice Baudelaire","Aunt Josephines sister"],"question":"Who is the Beatrice that writer Lemony Snicket always dedicates his books to?","type":"choice","answer":"Beatrice Baudelaire"},{"answers":["Settling on an island","Crying","Sailing on a boat","Dying"],"question":"The 13th book of A Series of Unfortunate Events ends with the Baudelaires doing what?","type":"choice","answer":"Sailing on a boat"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"The final 13th book of A Series of Unfortunate Events has 13 chapters and ends with an About the author... section.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Count Olaf, Mr. Baudelaire, Carmelita Spats","Violet Baudelaire, Jerome Squalor, Aunt Josephine","Violet Baudelaire, Klaus Baudelaire, Beatrice Snicket","Klaus Baudelaire, Sunny Baudelaire, Duncan Quagmire"],"question":"Which set of characters from A Series of Unfortunate Events contains only people who lived through the entire series?","type":"choice","answer":"Klaus Baudelaire, Sunny Baudelaire, Duncan Quagmire"},{"answers":["False","True"],"question":"Esme Squalors evilness was due to her boyfriend, Count Olaf.","type":"choice","answer":"False"},{"answers":["Ball game","Card game","Board game","Word game"],"question":"In A Series of Unfortunate Events, what type of game did Fionas brother invent?","type":"choice","answer":"Card game"},{"answers":["Jaques Snicket, Joseph Spat, Judy Spree","Jaques Snicket, Judy Spree, Justice Strauss","Jaques Snicket, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss","Joseph Spat, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss"],"question":"Which three names can J.S. stand for in the books of A Series of Unfortunate Events?","type":"choice","answer":"Jaques Snicket, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss"},{"answers":["Book 4","Book 5","Book 2","Book 3"],"question":"In which book of A Series of Unfortunate Events did Klauss glasses break?","type":"choice","answer":"Book 4"}]}}}